父亲愿意为儿子做任何事。
There is nothing a father wouldn't do for his son.
你妈妈从来都不明白。
Your mother never understood this.
她看着你，把你当成了怪物。
She looked at you and saw a monster.
我看到了潜力。
I saw potential.
当一个恶霸拿走了你的钱，你就拿走了他的眼睛。
When a bully took your money, you took his eye.
他们说你疯了，你就把他们的舌头割了。
When they called you crazy, you took their tongues.
但今天是我带你来的。
But I brought you here today.
是慷慨吗?
Was it generosity?
爱吗?
Love?
不。
No.
这样我创造的东西就不会随我而去。
It's so what I built doesn't die with me.
这样我的遗产才能流传下去，
So my legacy can live on,
因为父亲和儿子就是一切。
because a father and his son is everything.
我有一份只能托付给一个人的工作。
I have a job that I can only trust with one man.
你。
You.
我手下最残忍的士兵在监视我们的金库，
My most ruthless soldiers were watching our cash houses,
他们让这个多米尼克·托雷托烧了我的东西
and they let this Dominic Toretto burn what is mine.
我会杀了多米尼克·托雷托。
I'll kill Dominic Toretto.
我要把他们都杀了。
I'll kill 'em all.
杀了他们?你会宽恕他们吗?
Kill them? You'd show them mercy?
不，我的儿子。
No, my son.
当你欠下痛苦时，永远不要接受死亡作为回报。
When suffering is owed, never accept death as a payment.
让托雷托吃苦头。
Make Toretto suffer.
现在工作开始了。
Now the work begins.
在那里，
And in there,
今天我们要让我们的家族走上真正的权力之路。
today we'll put our family on a path to real power.
让我们开始吧。
Let's get started.
狗屎!
Shit!
嘿，他们人太多了!
Hey, there's too many of them!
-我们去不了了-你说得对。我们没有。
- We're not gonna make it. - You're right. We aren't.
-你是。-不，我不会离开你的
- You are. - No, I'm not leaving you.
现在，你按照计划去做。
Now, you stick with the plan.
这一直都是计划。
It was always the plan.
得到他。
Get him.
♪我的九在我的手里
- ♪ I got my nine in my hand
九只在我的手里，九只在我的手里
♪ Nine in my hand, nine in my hand ♪
♬我在工作，我从六月忙到六月
♪ I'm working, I hustle from June to June ♪
♬我留着那张4 -哦，像扫帚一样被扫过
♪ I keep that four-oh, get swept like a broom ♪
♬是啊，我是我的蛋糕，不是苏西Q
♪ Yeah, I'm 'bout my cake, no Suzy Q ♪
♬是的，我在捡砖头，喝着耶稣汁
♪ Yeah, I'm getting bricks, sipping Jesus juice ♪
♬残忍是帮派，我有一把砍刀
♪ Cutthroat be the gang, I keep a machete ♪
♬大声喊出我的主要婊子，她是最湿的
♪ And shout out my main bitch, she be the wettest ♪
♬钱在我心里，努力在我肚子里
♪ Money on my mind, wok hard in my belly ♪
♬年轻…有了我，像五彩纸屑一样蹦出来
♪ Young ... with me, pop out like confetti ♪
♬真正的街道……我有很好的信用，你
♪ Real street ... and I got good credit, yo ♪
♬踩油门，这些…没准备好。♪
♪ Foot on the gas, these ... ain't ready. ♪
你说对了。
You had it.
我没有。
I didn't have it.
B，没有人从终点线开始。
B, no one starts at the finish line.
你要有信心。
You got to have faith.
记住今天的课程。
Remember today's lesson.
找到那条线，
Find the line,
感受一下车，
feel the car,
让它飞吧。
and let it fly.
-害怕是正常的。
- It's okay to be afraid.
有时候恐惧是最好的老师。
Sometimes fear can be the best teacher.
我并不害怕。
I wasn't scared.
-每个人都会害怕，孩子。-你没有。
- Everyone gets scared, son. - You don't.
你什么都不怕。
You're not afraid of anything.
我们最好快点。
We better hurry.
-曾祖母刚飞过来。
- Great-Grandma just flew in.
她正在做她著名的马杜罗。
And she's making her famous maduros.
我们得赶在罗曼叔叔之前拿到那些东西。
We got to get to those before Uncle Roman does.
这才是让人害怕的。
Now, that's something to be afraid of.
♬带我回到那个我称之为我的城市
♪ Take me back to the city that I call my city ♪
♬在那里每个人都知道我的名字
♪ Where everybody knows my name ♪
♬带我回到我的爱人身边，yeah
♪ Take me back to the people that I call my people, yeah ♪
♬我离我的城市很远很远，我的城市
♪ I'm a long, long way from my city, my city ♪
噢噢，噢噢，噢噢
♪ Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh
♬从我的城市，我的城市…
♪ From my city, my city...
你已经死了。
You have been dead.
是时候让你活下去了。 告诉过你们，
- It's time to get you living. Told you guys,
我不需要那个
I don't need that.
好了，侧写完成了。
There, profile done.
不客气
You're welcome.
现在，你给它大约三四天……
Now, you give it about three, four days...
-它不会瞬间发生。
- It never happens instantly.
-等等，什么?嗯。
- Wait, what? Hmm.
哇。
Wow.
让我再看看你的头像。
Let me see your profile picture again.
他肯定在上面放了滤镜。
He must have put a filter on there.
你们在看什么?
What are you guys looking at?
-哦，等等。不，不，不。-只是电子游戏而已
- Oh, wait. No, no, no, no. - They're just video games, man.
-等等，伙计。-只是录像而已。
- H-H-Hold on, man. - Just videos, man.
我可以坐在你旁边吗?
Can I sit next to you?
男孩好管闲事。-你开始漂流了吗?
Boy nosy. - You drifting yet?
我是。
I am.
你真该看看我们的样子。太酷了，妈妈。
You should've seen us. It was so cool, Mom.
嘿!
Hey!
!¡Oye,家族!
!¡Oye, familia!
我饿死了!
I am starving!
-别这样。
- Come on.
我也想要每个人的拥抱
I also want a hug from every single person in--
哦。
Oh.
——啊。-你看到那条线了吗?
- Ah. - You see the line?
我们都在排队等待这份爱，奶奶。
We're all waiting in line for this love, abuelita.
-是啊。-等着尝尝这个。
- Oh, yeah. - Wait till you taste this.
真的很好吃。
It's really good.
我费了很大的劲。
I put myself out for this one.
——哦。
- Oh.
好了，大家安静点。
Okay, everybody pipe down, please.
阿布丽塔有话要说。
Abuelita would like to say something.
-请给我滚边和滚边。
- Piping and downing, please.
当我看着这个美好的家庭，
As I look out at this wonderful family,
我心中充满了骄傲。
I am filled with so much pride.
我儿子，你父亲的那种骄傲
The kind of pride that my son-- your father--
如果他在这里，我会很高兴的。
would have enjoyed if he were here.
我知道这条路很艰难
I know that this road has been very hard
也不公平。
and also not fair.
然而你却在这里
And yet here you are,
尽管困难重重，
despite all of the odds,
建造这座宏伟的建筑
building this magnificent
-腿…
- leg...
这是一份将代代相传的遗产。
It is a legacy that will go on for generations.
没有人能把它拿走。
No one can take it away.
不是现在。
Not now.
永远不会。
Not ever.
——是的!
- Yeah!
“。
To familia.
Familia.
真爱永远。总是这样。
Siempre. Always.
♬哥斯达黎加……
♪ Costa Rica...
嘿，这双新耐克鞋，伙计。别玩了!该死的……
Hey, these new Nikes, man. Stop playing! Goddamn...
拜托，罗曼。局里让你负责的
Come on, Roman. The agency put you in charge,
你说我可以开车的
and you said I get to drive.
看，我真正需要的
See, what I really need
我需要你的脑子
is I need your brain.
这是罗曼·皮尔斯从未说过的话。
Words Roman Pearce has never said.
再跟我说一遍。我需要细节。
So talk me through it again. I need details.
是啊，中情局得到了一些被盗军事装备的线索。
Yeah, the agency got a tip on some stolen military hardware.
明天，下一代量子计算机芯片
Tomorrow, a next-gen quantum computer chip
将被运送到罗马的大街小巷
will be transported through the streets of Rome,
他们需要我们去偷。
and they need us to steal it.
我查了罗曼的情报。
I checked Roman's intel.
这是合法的。
It's legit.
当然是合法的。
Of course it's legit.
我们说的是罗马。
We're talking 'bout Rome.
罗马。罗马。
Rome. Roman.
拜托，伙计。
Come on, man.
这就像在我家后院策划抢劫一样。
That's like planning a heist in my backyard.
你对罗马的唯一了解就是"罗马人"面条。
Only thing you know about Rome is "ro-man" noodles.
有一件事你没跟我们解释
One thing you didn't explain to us is:
我们干嘛要遥控车，
Why the hell do we need a RC car,
一辆金色的兰博基尼和12罐笑气?
a gold Lamborghini and 12 tanks of laughing gas?
是的，我加入，因为你绝对是
Yes, I'm in, 'cause you are definitely
你需要所有的大脑。
going to need all the brains you can get.
你在搞什么鬼。
You up to something.
嗨,罗马…-别跟我说话，伙计
Hey, Rome... - Don't talk to me, man.
别跟我说话。
Don't talk to me.
-好吧。-你知道吗?
- All right. - You know what?
这种不尊重得停止了。
The disrespect is gon' have to stop.
现在!
Now!
那只是我的。你知道我在说什么吗?
That's just my-- You know what I'm saying?
我只是在练习我的领导能力。
Me just, you know, practicing my leadership voice.
我知道怎么回事了。
I see what's going on.
泰吉，你以为你很狡猾，兄弟。
Tej, you think you slick, bro.
看看你。
Look at you.
监视我。
Spying on me.
这个旧船锚是怎么回事?
What's up with this old boat anchor?
没有燃油喷射。
No fuel injection.
我的意思是，我期望的是更大的
I mean, I'd expect something bigger
你也会更好，多姆。
and better from you, Dom.
小B和我一起建的。
Little B and I are building it together.
化油器迫使他倾听。
The carburetor forces him to listen.
这就是现在的问题。
That's the problem nowadays.
-没人再听了。-你最好小心点。
- Nobody listens anymore. - Well, you better watch out.
小个子会比我们所有人都好
Little man's gonna be a better wrench than any of us
到他12岁的时候。
by the time he's 12.
我是说，这才是重点，不是吗?
I mean, that's the whole point, isn't it?
把它传下去。
Pass it down.
一代比一代好。
Each generation better than the last.
这是真的。
That's true.
这是父亲。
That's fatherhood.
从我们俩开油罐车到现在已经有很长的路要走了
Come a long way from the two of us popping gas trucks
-在民主共和国，是吧?-当然了。
- in the D.R., huh? - We sure did.
那是一段艰难的时期。
Those were some tough times.
那是一段美好的时光。
Those were some great times.
哦,你……你们都在开会?
Oh, you... Y-Y'all was in a meeting?
-对不起。
- I'm sorry.
我不想打扰你们。
I-I ain't want to interrupt y'all.
阿憨，我们走吧。
Han, let's go, man.
罗曼问他是否可以领导这次任务。
Roman asked if he could lead this mission.
我怎么能拒绝他呢?
How could I tell him no?
但你知道我不能让他们独自去罗马。
But you know I can't let them go to Rome without you.
一生一世。
Los bandoleros for life.
祝你一生快乐。
Lo bandolero for life.
你尊重他的名字。
You honor his name.
把我们放在你心里……
Hold us in your heart...
…你永远不会迷失方向。
...and you will never lose your way.
你会比我好。
You will be better than me.
你在看什么?
What are you looking at?
你。
You.
♪天使……
♪ Angel...
-孩子睡着了。——嗯。
- Kid's asleep. - Mm-hmm.
♬我最终会把你拉下…♪
♪ I'll pull you down eventually... ♪
怎样才能变得更漂亮?
How do you get more beautiful?
♪像我这样的人打破了美好的事物，天使…♪
♪ People like me break beautiful things, angel... ♪
-到了吗?
- Is it here yet?
不。
No.
时机一到，它就会到来。毫米。
It'll come when the time is right. -Mm.
-♬像我这样的人分手了
- ♪ People like me break
♬美好的事物
♪ Beautiful things
♬我放弃一切只是为了减轻你的痛苦
♪ I give it all up to ease your pain ♪
♬是啊，我愿意整天这样做
♪ Yeah, I would do that all day ♪
♬我退出游戏是为了不让你受到伤害
♪ I stepped back from the game to keep you out of harm's way ♪
♬为游戏冒一切险，但这需要不止一个人♬
♪ Risk it all for the game, but it take more than one person ♪
♬两个人一个直到我有同样的感觉……♪
♪ Two people one till I feel the same... ♪
今天我们在车里的时候…
You know, when we were in the car today...
…B说:“爸爸，
...B said, "Daddy,
你从不害怕。”
you're never afraid."
但我是。
But I am.
我害怕失去儿子。
I'm afraid of losing a son.
或者是妻子。
Or a wife.
这种事不会再发生了。
That's not gonna happen again.
你想盯着后视镜就盯着吧。
You can keep your eyes on that rearview all you want.
但你知道你怀念什么吗?
But you know what you miss?
怎么啦？
What?
永恒
Eternity
在这一刻。
in this moment.
我和你一样惊讶。
I'm as surprised as you are.
我想象过无数次杀了你。
I've imagined killing you a thousand times.
上次有6英寸的强化玻璃，
Last time, there was six inches of reinforced glass,
——枪…… -不!
- guns... -  No!
…警卫。
...guards.
我当时联系不上你。
I couldn't reach you then.
现在我可以了。
Now I can.
你一定想听听我的遗言。
You're gonna want to hear my last words.
——Dom !——不!
- Dom! - -  No!
你听到埃琳娜的遗言了吗
Did you hear Elena's last words
在你杀她之前?
before you killed her?
那你不觉得我来这有什么好理由吗?
Then don't you think I'd have a goddamn good reason to be here?
也许这是你在意的唯一原因。
Maybe the only reason that's ever mattered to you.
莱蒂[低声说]:小B。
LETTY [whispers]: Little B.
醒醒，亲爱的。
Wake up, sweetie.
我们有一位不速之客。
We have an unwanted guest.
你知道该怎么做。
You know what to do.
你想要什么?
What is it that you want?
说话。
Speak.
今晚我遇到魔鬼了。
I met the devil tonight.
说实话，我一直以为是我。
Honestly, I always thought it was me.
这有点令人失望。
So that was kind of disappointing.
他来到我家门口。
He came to my door.
他不请自来。
He let himself in.
他们说当你面对死亡时
They say when you're facing death,
你的一生在你眼前闪过。
your life flashes before your eyes.
他们是对的吗?
Are they right?
我会从你是谁说起。
I'd start with who you are.
一个大多数人一辈子都无法回答的问题。
A question most can't answer in a lifetime.
你有三秒钟的时间。
You have three seconds.
在你在我沙发上失血过多之前，
Before you bleed out on my couch,
你最好解释一下你为什么来这里。
you might want to explain why you're here.
我在这里
I'm here
因为敌人
because the enemy
我的敌人
of my enemy
是你自己。
is you.
我是一个有
I am a man with
没有名字。
no name.
一无所有。
Heir to nothing.
我来这里的原因和你一样。
And I'm here for the same reasons you are.
多米尼克Toretto。
Dominic Toretto.
你想杀多姆?
You want to kill Dom?
整个街区都排着队。
Line's around the block.
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
如果有痛苦，永远不要接受死亡。
Never accept death when suffering is owed.
但我需要你的帮助。
But I need your help.
你的玩具和科技产品。
Your toys and your tech.
你的孩子们。
All your boys.
因为你要么和我在一起，要么…
'Cause you're either with me or you're...
我和别人玩得不好。
I don't play well with others.
那你就得看着你最爱的人死去。
Then you'll have to watch who you love most die.
你看着的是我最爱的人。
You're looking at who I love most.
你以为你可以用我的招式来对付我吗?
You thought you could use my own move against me?
我不是在跟你说话。
I wasn't talking to you.
我在和齐克说话。
I was talking to Zeke.
阿米尔。
Amir.
凯文的父亲。
Kevin's dad.
会是谁呢?
Who could it be?
可爱的孩子们。
Cute kids.
哦。
Ooh.
他们都有东西可拿
They all had something to take
除了那个可怜的混蛋。
except that poor bastard.
甚至连一只小猫都没有。
Not even a kitty cat.
剩下的人有个选择。
The rest of you have a choice.
我还是……
Me or...
你想要控制世界。
You want to control the world.
我只是想惩罚它。
I just want to punish it.
我会记住的。
I will remember this.
我想每个人都会的。
I think everyone will.
嗯。我需要有人帮我操作，不是吗?
Huh. I need someone to help me operate this, don't I?
书呆子吗?
Nerds?
跟我来。
Come with me.
好了，你知道该怎么做
All right, you know what to do
如果你想再见到你的家人。
if you want to see your families again.
再见。
Ciao.
杀了她。
Kill her.
大便。
Shit.
你以为我会相信你吗?
Did you think I would trust you?
现在很难找到好的帮手。
It is hard finding good help these days.
一场战争即将来临。
There's a war coming.
双方正在选择。
The sides are being chosen.
你爱的每个人都会被毁灭。
And everyone you love will be destroyed.
流了六品脱血。
Lost six pints of blood.
正常人四岁就死了。
Normal person dies at four.
我们要把她送回黑牢。
We're shipping her back to our black site.
-她可能撑不过去了-但她的故事证实了吗?
- She may not make it. - But did her story check out?
我们确认了市中心的枪击事件
We confirmed the shooting downtown,
但她的技术并不在那里。
but her tech wasn't there.
拿走它的人现在有了电子武器。
And whoever took it now has an electronic arsenal.
-你通知你的人了?-是的，米娅和布莱恩很安全。
- You've alerted your people? - Yeah, Mia and Brian are safe.
我试着联系罗曼，泰吉，拉姆齐，阿憨。
I tried to get in touch with Roman, Tej, Ramsey, Han.
-没人接。-知道他们可能在哪里吗?
- No answer. - Any idea where they might be?
在罗马。
In Rome.
为你工作。
Working for you.
多姆，我们不…我们在罗马没有任务。
Dom, we don't... we don't have a mission in Rome.
这是一个圈套。
It's a setup.
大便。
Shit.
我们要去罗马。
We're going to Rome.
-跟我来。-是的，先生。
- Follow me. - Yes, sir.
儿子，你和我一起去上驾驶课。
Son, you and I will finish that driving lesson.
这是一个承诺。
It's a promise.
不管发生什么。
No matter what happens.
我总是遵守我的诺言。
And I always keep my promises.
回去吧。
Head back up.
由ANNA, MadMan和Gemitaiz演奏]
" by ANNA, MadMan and Gemitaiz playing]
♬嗨，安娜
♪ Ehi, ANNA
♬我爱你，我爱你
♪ Ci beccavamo nel bando, sopra il Booster ♪
♬安娜的命运是不可能的，不可能的
♪ ANNA fattura e no, non parlo di buste ♪
♬我爱你，我爱你
♪ Mando tutto io, svuota il freezer ♪
♬我想要的是一段关于音乐的故事。♪
♪ C'ho il passaggio assicurato sopra questo diesel... ♪
所以有人能帮我理解吗
So can somebody please help me understand
我们是怎么实施手机抢劫的
how we're pulling off a mobile heist
但我都不能开车吗
but I don't even get to drive?
我们越早撬开卡车偷芯片，
Well, the sooner we break into the truck and steal the chip,
你越早过上美好的生活，好吗?
the sooner you get to live la dolce vita, okay?
♬在fila…
♪ Infami tornano in fila...
罗曼，车队快就位了。
Roman, the convoy's almost in position.
你到底在哪儿?
Where the hell are you at?
你应该避开干扰。
You're supposed to be running interference.
rome - rome 's in the building
Romey-Rome's in the building.
-你看到我闪耀，宝贝。
- You see me shining, baby.
我们在执行我的任务。
We on my mission now.
我们都知道这是你的任务。
Yeah, we all know that this is your mission.
因为地球上没人会让阿憨坐阿尔法。
'Cause nobody else on Earth would put Han in an Alfa.
如果罗曼不在，我们早就到了
You know, we'd already be there if Roman wasn't
用轮子驾驶诺克斯堡
driving Fort Knox on wheels.
你知道这里面有什么，宝贝。
You know what's under this hood, baby.
这辆车坏了。
This car is sick.
这老女人缺乏马力，
What this old girl lacks in horsepower,
她的敏捷弥补了这一点。
she makes up for in agility.
是的，这是真的。
Yeah, it's true.
而兰博基尼是V-10发动机
While the Lamborghini has a V-10
配备Stage 3 UGR双涡轮增压套件，
with a Stage 3 UGR twin-turbo kit,
阿尔法在这种环境下绝对有优势。
the Alfa will definitely have an advantage in this environment.
怎么啦？
What?
哦，对了。我现在知道了。
Oh, that's right. I know stuff now.
-你愿意嫁给我吗?
- Will you marry me?
就这样吗?
That's all it took?
♬女高音助推器
♪ Bando sopra il Booster
♬安娜的命运是不可能的，不可能的
♪ ANNA fattura e no, non parlo di buste ♪
♬中文教程…
♪ Mando tutto io...
所有那些代理玩具，
All those agency toys,
你还是联系不到罗曼?
and you still can't reach Roman?
不准打电话，不准发邮件，不准发短信。
No cell phone, emails or text messages.
一切正常
Nothing's going through.
我甚至试着在阿憨的约会软件上右滑。
I even tried swiping right on Han's dating app.
是谁派他去执行这个假任务的
Whoever sent him on this bogus mission
确定我们不能警告他们。
made for damn sure we couldn't warn them.
继续搜索。他们接近。
Keep searching. They're close.
好了，各位，表演时间到了。
All right, everybody, showtime.
-我们走吧!
- Here we go!
。
In position.
提示小Tej。
Cue Tiny Tej.
等等，等等，等等。举起。小Tej吗?
Wait, wait, wait. Hold up. Tiny Tej?
你在说什么，罗曼?-
What are you talking about, Roman? -
好了，好了，开火!
All right, all right, fire 'em up!
我们一直没有达成一致。
We never agreed on that.
你说你想开车。现在轮到你开车了。
You said you wanted to drive. Now you driving.
你笑什么呢?不要……-
What are you laughing at? Don't... -
你从哪弄来的?
Where'd you even get that?
你知道吗，小泰吉的大脑?
Just so you know, Tiny Tej's brain?
比你的还大。
Still bigger than yours.
Back is blind.
小心，女士们。这不关你的事!
Watch out, ladies. This ain't "nun" ya business!
是闪耀的时候了!
It's time to shine!
我们在。我有轮子。
We're in. I have the wheel.
我们被锁在里面了!
We're locked inside!
卡车被遥控了。
The truck's being steered remotely.
一个1，一个2，一个…
And a one, and a two, and a...
神圣的狗屎!发生了什么事? !
Holy shit! What happened?!
放太多了吧?准备好了吗?
Put a little too much in, huh? Ready?
太棒了!
That was awesome!
哦。
Ooh.
Scusi !
Scusi!
他们在偷我们的卡车。
They're stealing our truck.
和我们一起进去。
And with us inside.
刚收到报告，论坛附近发生两起爆炸。
Just got reports of two explosions near the Forum.
这是他们。
That's them.
准备好了吗?和…
Ready? And...
-等等，你听到了吗?
- Wait, you hear that?
-那是什么鬼东西?-我不知道!
- What the hell is that?! - I have no idea!
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
那是个大炸弹!
That's a big-ass bomb!
——什么?——炸弹!
- What? - Bomb!
罗曼，你说这是装筹码的
Roman, you said this was carrying chips
对于一台超级计算机来说。
for a supercomputer.
那不是芯片。是个炸弹!
That is not a chip. It's a bomb!
如果它爆炸了怎么办?
What happens if it goes off?
什么叫"万一爆炸了怎么办"
What do you mean, "What happens if it goes off?"
罗马的七座山将会减少到两座半!
The Seven Hills of Rome will be down to two and a half!
全城被毁，无数人丧生。
City-wide devastation, countless lives lost.
你知道的，就是炸弹的作用。
You know, the thing bombs do.
我们来找你。
We're coming to you.
好了，呆子们。我们炸的是什么?
All right, dorks. What are we blowing up?
怎么啦？
What?
梵蒂冈吗?
The Vatican?
哇。
Wow.
好吧。我来做。
Okay. I'll do it.
但你们会下地狱的。
But you guys are going to hell.
那是他们的卡车。
That's their truck.
哦，谢天谢地。Dom,莱蒂。
Oh, thank God. Dom, Letty.
哦。看看谁来了。
Ooh. Look who's here.
你来得正是时候，多米尼克。
You're right on time, Dominic.
关掉加密收音机。
Turn off the encrypted radio.
拉姆齐吗?
Ramsey?
我们被遥控了。船上有炸弹。
We're being remote-controlled. There's a bomb on board.
这是DM-79型水下高当量中子水雷。
It's a DM-79 subnautical high-yield neutron mine.
啊!找到了。
Ah! Found it.
我可以用中情局的自动开关解除它。
I can disarm it with an agency kill switch.
我只需要你亲自动手。
I just need physical hands on the device.
-我们得拦住那辆卡车。-抱歉，美国队长。
- We have to stop that truck. - Sorry, Captain America.
我不能让你这么做。
Can't let you do that.
我们得快点了!卡车正在加速。
We got to hurry! The truck is speeding up.
-我们得堵住它的路-我要赶在它前面
- We got to block its path. - I'm gonna get ahead of it.
拉姆齐，泰吉，系好安全带。
Ramsey, Tej, strap in.
声呐喊。
Whoop.
Ah-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta。
Ah-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
多姆，说吧!我捏!
Dom, go ahead! I'm pinched!
多米尼克。
Dominic.
来吧!
Come on!
该死，他跑得真快。
Damn it, he's fast.
真的吗?晾衣绳吗?
Really? The clothesline?
我们不能开它
Well, we can't drive it,
看来我们只能放手了。
guess we're just gonna have to roll it.
神圣的狗屎!卡车要翻山了!
Holy shit! The truck's about to go over the hill!
-我们得撞进去。-我们必须什么?
- We have to crash into it. - We have to what?!
我很抱歉，我的宝贝!
I'm so sorry, my gold baby!
它停不下来!
It's not stopping!
Dom，炸弹出来了。
Dom, the bomb is out.
所有人，保持距离。我来吧。
Everybody, stay clear. I got this.
不。我们可以的。
No. We got this.
莱蒂!
Letty!
我们把他们都变成恐怖分子了吗?
Have we made them all terrorists?
他们的照片已被提交给当局。
Their images have been fed to the authorities.
好了，鲍勃!我得去杀了那个混蛋
All right, Bob! I got to go kill that jerk
那是在拆除我的炸弹。
that's trying to disarm my bomb.
总有事情发生，你知道吗?哦。
It's always something, you know? Oh.
记住，你们的家人还在我手上，你们哪儿也别去。
Remember, I still have your families, so don't go anywhere.
Buongiorno,罗马!
Buongiorno, Roma!
好吧。
All right.
伙计，那是谁啊?
Man, who the hell is that?
嘿!他来了!
Hey! There he is!
风云人物。罗曼·皮尔斯，队长。
Man of the hour. Roman Pearce, team leader.
等不及想看你从这案子里出来了。
Can't wait to see you get out of this one.
但丁(唱):哦，莱蒂!
DANTE [singsongy]: Oh, Letty!
我想我找到那个人了。
I think I found our guy.
嘿,莱蒂。 Vaffanculo !
Hey, Letty. Vaffanculo!
我在追他。
I'm on him.
泵要爆了。
That pump's gonna blow.
小人物，你起来了。
Little Nobody, you're up.
-移动到…——躲躲猫!
- Moving to dis... - Peekaboo!
快出来!要爆炸了!-哦,大便。
Get out of there! It's gonna blow! -Oh, shit.
——繁荣。
- Boom.
我们现在就得堵住引爆器。
We need to jam the detonator now.
我知道了，我知道了。蕾蒂，别跟丢了。
I got it, I got it. Letty, don't lose him.
我可以锁定你的位置并传送
I can lock on to your location and transmit
通过手机的蜂窝干扰。
cellular interference through your phone.
这样能干扰他的引爆器，为我们争取时间。
That should jam his detonator and buy us some time.
莱蒂。
Letty.
万岁!
Bravo!
伙计们，这很棘手。
It's getting tricky, guys.
我不能再盯着他了。
I can't stay on him for much longer.
拉姆齐，那条河有多深?
Ramsey, how deep is that river?
台伯河吗?嗯…
The Tiber? Uh...
呃，60英尺。
Uh, 60 feet.
我是说，水可能会窒息爆炸，
I mean, the water could smother the explosion,
也许可以把它的功率降低十倍。
reduce its power by ten times, maybe.
该死的!
Damn it!
你太想我了，宝贝!
You missed me by that much, baby!
我跟丢了他。他走了。
I lost him. He's gone.
该死的!
Damn!
我们找不到他了。
He's out of our reach.
我们不能再干扰信号了。
We can't jam the signal anymore.
坏消息，多姆。我又回来了。
Bad news, Dom. I'm back in business.
你有30秒的时间拯救罗马。
You got 30 seconds to save Rome.
Dom，他启动了炸弹，你就快到河边了。
Dom, he armed the bomb, and you're almost at the river.
15秒，多姆。
15 seconds, Dom.
多姆，听我说。
Dom, listen to me.
梵蒂冈在爆炸范围内。
The Vatican's within the blast radius.
离开那里。
Get out of there.
你已经尽力了。
You've done everything you could.
不是万能的。
Not everything.
五。
Five.
四。
Four.
三。
Three.
。
Two.
One.
我们做了什么?
What have we done?
通过你的痛苦，我将完成我的使命。
Through your suffering, I'll fulfill my destiny.
来找我吧。
Come find me.
你的痛苦才刚刚开始。
Your pain has just begun.
再见，多姆。
I'll see you soon, Dom.
来自意大利的突发新闻。
Breaking news from Italy.
首都罗马发生大规模爆炸。
The capital Rome has been hit by a massive explosion.
…成为一种大型军事武器
...to be a large military weapon.
梵蒂冈坚持
The Vatican has sustained
一些结构损坏。
some structural damage.
…但没有人因此丧生。
...but no lives were claimed.
当局已经确认恐怖分子是
Authorities have identified the terrorists as
-这五个人。
- these five individuals.
…这五个人，由这个人领导。
...as these five individuals, led by this man.
-多米尼克·托雷托。——Toretto。-Toretto。
- Dominic Toretto. - Toretto. -Toretto.
-多米尼克·托雷托。多米尼克Toretto。
- Dominic Toretto. Dominic Toretto.
执法部门正在跨境开展工作，
Law enforcement is working across borders,
动员国际追捕逃犯
mobilizing an international fugitive hunt
——规模空前。对不起，先生。
- of unprecedented scale. I'm sorry, sir.
-我不知道她是怎么进来的-是的。
- I don't know how she got in. - I do.
我偷了你的警徽。
I stole your badge.
不过，我现在受够了。谢谢。
I'm done with it now, though. Thanks.
好吧，如果不是，嗯
Well, if it isn't, um--
说实话，我不知道该怎么称呼你。
Honestly, I-I don't know what to call you.
无名小卒?
Little Miss Nobody?
你叫我的真名怎么样?
How about you call me by my actual name?
据我所知，苔丝，你在大马士革负责行动。
Last I heard, Tess, you were running ops in Damascus.
你以为你能走进这个房间
You think you can walk in this room
就因为你爸爸是经纪公司的传奇人物吗?
just 'cause your daddy's an agency legend?
我来这是因为有人需要说话
I'm here because someone needs to speak
我代表辩方。
on behalf of the defense.
刚刚在罗马发生的事是一场彻头彻尾的灾难。
What just happened in Rome was an unmitigated disaster.
伤亡人数被控制在最低限度，
Casualties were kept to a minimum,
但其影响是全球性的。
but the impact was global.
你觉得在意大利发生了什么?
And what do you think happened in Italy?
观光，吃意大利面，
Oh, sightseeing, eating bucatini,
-偷一颗两万吨的炸弹。-得了吧，艾姆斯
- stealing a 20-kiloton bomb. - Oh, come on, Aimes.
那是胡扯，你知道的。小心,现在。
That's bullshit and you know it. -Careful, now.
“小人物”出了问题
With Little Nobody out of commission
你爸爸失踪了，你在跟新老板说话。
and your daddy in the wind, you're talking to the new boss.
好戏上演。
Showtime.
2001年，洛杉矶。
Los Angeles, 2001.
卑微的出身，当地的孩子，
Humble roots, local kids,
街头赛车手变成了劫机者。
street racers who became hijackers.
升级到高速走私，
Graduated to high-speed smuggling,
手机越狱，火车抢劫。
mobile jailbreaks, train robberies.
如果可以在汽车上完成，他们就会这样做。
If it could be done in a car, they did it.
如果它违反了上帝的法则和万有引力，他们就做了两次。
If it violates the laws of God and gravity, they did it twice.
你自己写的?
You write that yourself?
我们第一次注意到是在2011年，
We first took notice in 2011,
在里约，他们抢劫了大毒枭赫南·雷耶斯，
Rio, when they robbed a drug kingpin, Hernan Reyes,
把他的尸体留在桥上。
left his body on a bridge.
我的前任，无名先生，看到了潜力，
My predecessor, Mr. Nobody, saw potential,
于是他招募了他们，当然是自由职业者。
so he recruited them-- freelance, of course.
他们在阿布扎比为我们执行任务，
They ran missions for us in Abu Dhabi,
东京，伦敦，纽约，第比利斯。
Tokyo, London, New York, Tbilisi.
要我说，我们几年前就该断绝关系，
You ask me, we should've cut ties years back,
但他们有自己的冠军。
but they had their champions.
这是他们的作案手法
That's their M.O.
腐败执法。
To corrupt law enforcement.
Brian O ' conner。
Brian O'Conner.
埃琳娜•内维斯。路加福音霍布斯。
Elena Neves. Luke Hobbs.
每个人都成了家人。
Everyone becomes family.
就像一个有汽车的邪教。
It's like a cult with cars.
就连苔丝亲爱的爸爸也不例外。
Even Tess's dear old dad.
所以我们都只是
So we're all just
烧烤和啤酒远离腐败?
a barbecue and a beer away from corruption?
你想说什么?
What's your point?
重点是他们是罪犯。
Point is they're criminals.
罗马只是个时间问题。
Rome was a matter of time.
他们偷了上亿美元
They've stolen hundreds of millions of dollars
以及至少一艘核潜艇。
and at least one nuclear sub.
真正的问题是:我们怎么能让这种情况持续这么久?
The real question is: How did we let this go on so long?
这个家族为了保持我们的清白不惜弄脏自己的手。
This family has gotten their hands dirty to keep ours clean.
他们为了这个机构去了地狱之门又回来了。
They've driven to the gates of hell and back for this agency.
罗马有些地方不对劲。
Something is not right with Rome.
这不可能。
It can't be.
它可以，也确实如此。
It can and it is.
该机构比这要好。
The agency is better than this.
我们比这更聪明。
We are smarter than this.
我们应该支持多姆和他的家人。
We should be standing with Dom and his family.
这是我们能做的最起码的事。
That is the very least that we can do.
如果我们不采取行动，我们所有人都会受到打击。
If we don't act, this blows back on all of us.
其后果将是存在的。
The fallout will be existential.
我要申请完全的授权。
I'm asking for full green-light authority.
用任何手段杀死或捕获托雷托家族。
Kill or capture the Toretto clan by any means.
艾姆斯，你在干什么?
Aimes, what are you doing?
看来是眼睛在作怪。
Looks like the ayes have it.
作为你的顶头上司
As your direct superior,
我才不管别人有多善良，
I don't give a shit about anybody's heart of gold,
我讨厌烧烤。
and I hate barbecues.
你知道我会让货运火车走土路，
You know I'd make a freight train take a dirt road,
所以别挡我的路。
so do not get in my way.
好吧。
Okay.
我要走我自己的路。
I'll go my own way.
♬我的世界已经沦陷
♪ My world has fallen
♬我要双膝跪地
♪ I'm falling to my knees
♬哦，耶
♪ Oh, yeah
♬现在我感到我的手在颤抖
♪ And now I feel my hands trembling ♪
♬哦，上帝
♪ Oh, Lord
♬我不能保证我会再呼吸一次。♪
♪ Ain't no promise I'll breathe again. ♪
罗马覆灭，世界也覆灭。
When Rome falls, so does the world.
这可不是什么罗马节日。
Well, it ain't no Roman holiday.
你也不是格里高利·派克。
And you're no Gregory Peck.
毫米。
Mm.
我的家人吗?
My family?
你的人都躲起来了。他们现在是安全的。
Your team's gone to ground. They're safe for now.
他们抓走了蕾蒂。
They've taken Letty.
-他们是谁?-机构。
- Who's they? - The agency.
而你刚刚跃居第一
And you've just shot to number one
在世界头号通缉犯名单上。
on the world's most wanted list.
干这事的人想切断你和中情局的联系
Whoever did this wanted to sever your ties to the agency
把你和家人隔离开来。
and isolate you from your family.
任何联系你们的人都会被追踪。
Any attempt to contact your team will be traced.
我要你带个口信给无名先生。
I need you to get a message to Mr. Nobody.
你需要一个灵媒或者魔术师。
You'll need a medium for that or a magician.
他已经消失了。
He's done his disappearing act.
把消息传出去。
Just get the message out.
告诉他我准备好要那个比利时人了，
Tell him I'm ready to have that Belgian,
他会知道该去哪里。
and he'll know where to go.
我有话要告诉你，宝贝。
I've got a message for you, ducky.
世界着火了，你还想继续逃跑
The world is on fire, and you want to keep running
进入燃烧的大楼去救人，
into the burning building to save lives,
但最终大楼会倒塌在你身上。
but eventually the building's gonna collapse on you.
我不在乎死。
I don't care about dying.
我只关心保护我爱的人。
I only care about protecting the people that I love.
你知道为什么角斗士从来没有家庭吗?
You know why gladiators never had families?
——为什么?-因为他们知道
- Why? - Because they knew
每一天都可能是他们的最后一天。
that every day might be their last.
你选择了一条孤独的路，亲爱的。
You're choosing a lonely way, my darling.
不能带任何人一起去。
Can't take anyone with you.
让上帝之眼上线。
Bring God's Eye online.
是，长官，启动。
Yes, sir. Initiating.
告诉我托雷托和其他人的位置
Get me Toretto and the others' locations
精确到毫米。
to the millimeter.
先生，我们有麻烦了。
Sir, we have a problem.
上帝之眼追踪硬件被移除。
The God's Eye tracking hardware has been removed.
苔丝。
Tess.
我猜她的来访不完全是社交拜访。
I guess her visit wasn't purely a social call.
帮我个忙。
Do me a favor.
她一出现，我们就看看她去哪了。
She pops up on any grid, let's see where she goes.
至于其他人，我们的逃犯也不是未知数。
As for the rest, our fugitives aren't unknown quantities.
托雷托有一个妹妹，一个儿子。
Toretto has a sister, a son.
在我们找到他之前
Until we find him,
找到他的家人。
find his family.
哦!
Oh!
——再一次。
- Again.
哇。
Wow.
你是不是背叛了你最喜欢的阿姨?
Are you cheating on-on your favorite auntie?
你赢一英寸还是一英里都没关系。
It doesn't matter if you win by an inch or a mile.
赢得的胜利。
Winning's winning.
我在哪儿听过这句话?
Where have I heard that one before?
走吧!走吧!
Go! Go!
搜索无处不在!我们需要他们活着!
Search everywhere! We need them alive!
趴在地上!趴在地上!
Get on the ground! Get on the ground!
不!米娅!放开她!
No! Mia! Let her go!
快跑!
Run!
-怎么了?-雅各布叔叔?
- What's up? - Uncle Jakob?
你爸爸派我来的。
Your dad sent me.
计划有变。
Change of plans.
不要动!
Don't move!
-我说不许动!
- I said don't move!
你有小B吗?
Do you have Little B?
B !
B!
——冻结!
- Freeze!
-你没事吧?-是的。
- You okay? - Yeah.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
B !
B!
来了,来了。
Come, come.
那些家伙到底是谁?
Who the hell were those guys?
机构。罗马是个陷阱。整个家庭都成了目标。
Agency. Rome was a trap. Whole family's being targeted.
好了，我得去找布莱恩和孩子们…
Okay, I got to get to Brian and the kids...
多姆让我来带走他。
Dom sent me to take him.
记得我们说过要去的地方吗
Remember that place we said we'd go
如果世界变成地狱?
if the world went to hell?
多姆想让团队在那里集合。
Dom wants the team to meet there.
是的。
Yeah.
好,看。
Okay, look.
小B，你和雅各布叔叔一起去。
Little B, you're gonna go with Uncle Jakob.
好吧?他说什么你就做什么。是吗?
Okay? You do whatever he says. Yeah?
我带你去找你爸爸。如果你不介意的话。
I'm gonna get you to your dad. If that's okay with you.
用你的生命保护他。
Protect him with your life.
我爱你，杰克。
I love you, Jakey.
我也爱你，姐姐。
I love you, too, sis.
我们开始吧。
Let's do it.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
哟!
Yo!
不是那个。
It's not that one.
就是这个。
It's this one.
是的。
Yep.
等等,但是…
Wait, but...
嗯?
Hmm?
♬嗨，我爱你
♪ Ehi, ci ho provato
一个自由的军队有一种平静的感觉
♪ A liberarmi da quel senso di indesiderato ♪
♬我爱你，我爱你，我爱你，我爱你
♪ Ed ho fallito mille volte peroò ci ho provato ♪
♬我爱你，我爱你，我爱你
♪ Ho messo pesi sulla schiena e poi sono caduto ♪
♬没有人会喜欢我的音乐，所以我喜欢你的音乐
♪ Ho perso sangue dal naso e mi sono rialzato ♪
♬Peroò a vent'an anni gigio mi chiedo do so troppo stand♬
♪ Peroò a vent'anni già mi chiedo se son troppo stanco ♪
♬我喜欢你的服务è我喜欢你想要的♬
♪ Se quello che mi serve è quello che ho desiderato ♪
♬Se ungiorno riusciroò davvero和esser实现…♪
♪ Se un giorno riusciroò davvero ad esser realizzato... ♪
我在找人。
I'm looking for someone.
你们俩看起来很想喝一杯。
You boys look like you could use a drink.
我请你喝一杯怎么样?嗯?
How about a round on me? Huh?
事实上，
As a matter of fact,
他们能买多少我就买多少。
I will buy as many rounds as they can handle.
♬我不喜欢你的守护神piuù我喜欢你cioò我喜欢你的守护神
♪ Ho scelto di guardare piuù avanti di cioò che vedo ♪
♬我爱你，我爱你
♪ Il mio passato non me lo scordo ♪
♬我爱你，我爱你，我爱你……♪
♪ Non lo rinnego, colpisci forte, tanto... ♪
照片吗?没有?
Shots? No?
照片吗?
Shots?
啤酒。两个。
Beers. Two of 'em.
谢谢。
Thanks.
欢呼。
Cheers.
奎妮告诉我能在这里找到你。
Queenie told me I could find you here.
比利时吗?
Belgian?
无名先生说他有个女儿。
Mr. Nobody said he had a daughter.
他做了吗?
He did?
既然他失踪了
Well, now that he's gone missing,
我从寒冷中走了进来。
I came in from the cold.
你爸爸管理着局里。
Your dad kept the agency in line.
现在感觉所有的锚都被切断了。
Now it feels like all the anchors have been cut.
在一个没有规则的世界里，没有人是安全的。
In a world where there is no code, no one's safe.
你是对的。
You're right.
该机构背弃了它所坚持的一切。
The agency has turned its back on everything it stood for.
新老板艾姆斯，他会带着一切来找你的。
The new boss, Aimes, he's coming for you with everything.
我在为你争取时间。
I'm buying you some time.
还借了他们的小追踪器。
And borrowed their, uh, little tracking device thingy.
看起来熟悉吗?
Look familiar?
上帝的眼睛。——嗯。
God's Eye. - Mm-hmm.
我会把它放在保险库里。
I'd put that in a vault somewhere.
人们把保险库从墙上拉出来，所以我觉得和我在一起更安全。
People pull vaults out of walls, so I think it's safer with me.
我截取了一个屏幕截图
I pulled a screen grab
他们错过的一段交通监控录像，
off of a traffic cam that they missed,
把它放在上帝的眼睛里。
put it in God's Eye.
在里约发生了一起谋杀案。
There was a hit in Rio.
你在里约不会有什么敌人吧?
You wouldn't happen to have any enemies in Rio, would you?
——雷耶斯。-赫南·雷耶斯?
- Reyes. - Hernan Reyes?
还没死，但他有个儿子，丹特。
Still pretty dead, but he has a son, Dante.
所以你得带我去里约。
So you're gonna have to get me to Rio.
这是你的第二个愿望。你还有一个。
That's your second wish. You have one more.
莱蒂。
Letty.
莱蒂被关在地图上没有的秘密监狱里。
Letty's in a black site prison off of every map.
那就把她弄出来。
Then get her out.
没有人能做到。
Nobody can.
没有人会。
Nobody would.
多姆，我很抱歉
Dom, I'm so sorry,
但你让我做的事是不可能的。
but what you're asking me to do is impossible.
没有什么是不可能的。
Nothing's impossible.
你只需要有信心。
You just have to have faith.
把我们藏在集装箱里偷偷带出罗马
Sneaking us out of Rome in a shipping container
满是须后水，这主意太糟糕了，罗曼。
full of aftershave, that was a terrible idea, Roman.
等等，我想我失去了嗅觉。
Wait, I think I lost my sense of smell.
那不是须后水。那是催泪瓦斯。
That is not aftershave. That is tear gas.
伙计，我不知道你们在说什么。
Hey, man, I don't know what y'all are talking about.
你懂我的意思吗?
You know what I mean?
我闻到了魔法的味道。
I smell magic.
我给自己拿了一瓶。
I took a bottle for myself.
这都要感谢你。
This is all thanks to you.
你知道的，对吧?
You know that, right?
不，你只要跟着我的"尾巴"做"尾巴"就行了
No, see, you just got to follow my "leat" as a "leater."
你明白我的意思吗?我是天生的“皮匠”。
You see what I'm saying? I'm a natural-born "leater."
我们在哪里?
Where are we?
我带你回家了，拉姆齐。
I brought you back home, Ramsey.
拥有最多监控摄像头的城市。
The city with the most amount of surveillance cameras.
完美的。
Perfect.
-爸爸知道你开这车吗?-他应该。
- Dad know you drive this thing? - He should.
我和他比赛。
I raced him in it.
正如你所知，在90年代，
And just so you know, in the '90s,
如果你的分数是5.0，那就意味着你是那个男人。
if you were rolling in a 5.0, it meant you were the man.
不管你喜不喜欢，它仍然是一个“斯坦”。
Like it or not, it's still a 'Stang.
所以，你知道，尊重。
So, you know, respect.
你知道吗?
You know what?
旅行的音乐。
Traveling music.
现在我们来看看回报
♪ Now we come to the payoff
♬这是一种很好的振动……♪
♪ It's such a good vibration... ♪
我13岁的时候买了这辆车。
I got this car when I was 13.
我自己重新粉刷的。也重新组装了马达。
Did the repaint myself. Rebuilt the motor, too.
啊。有时候你就是控制不了自己喜欢的东西，孩子。
Ah. Sometimes you just can't help what you love, kid.
你要告诉我我们要去哪吗?
Are you gonna tell me where we're going?
我的一个地方，你爸爸知道。
A place of mine your dad knows.
我们在那里见他。
We're gonna meet him there.
他没事吧?
So he's okay?
我们在那里见他。
We'll meet him there.
♬哟，是时候把它带出来了
♪ Yo, it's about that time to bring forth ♪
-♬节奏和韵律
- ♪ The rhythm and the rhyme
♬我要得到我的，那就得到你的
♪ I'm-a get mine, so get yours
♬我想感受到汗水从你的毛孔里冒出来
♪ I wanna feel sweat coming out your pores ♪
♬在房子里…
♪ On the house...
这家伙是个内衣模特。
This guy was an underwear model.
——什么?-是的。哦,是的。
- What? -  Yeah. Oh, yeah.
我们开始……
Here we go and...
小B，把它拿回来。这是一个回旋镖。
Little B, bring it back. It's a boomerang.
也许这是一个回旋镖。
It's a boomerang, maybe.
啊…
Ah...
哦!看看你!
Oh! Look at you!
这就是感觉。
That's feeling it.
这叫做感受振动。
That's called feeling the vibrations.
这只是能量，伙计。它的能量。这是振动。
It's just energy, man. It's energy. It's vibrations.
觉得它!感觉它!
Feel it! Feel it!
-♬来吧，来吧…-拜托!来吧!
- ♪ Come on, come on... - Come on! Come on!
你安全了，局长。
You're clear, Director.
华丽的外衣。
Fancy coat.
昂贵的耳环。
Expensive earrings.
那一定很疼。
Those got to hurt.
你真是使出了杀手锏啊?
You really brought out the big guns, huh?
我不是为中情局来的。
I'm not here for the agency.
你可以没收它。
You could've confiscated that.
你左手腕上的伤疤
That scar on your left wrist,
你遇到多姆的那晚得到的。
you got it the night you met Dom.
他说他是在炫耀。
He said he was showing off.
我在音频里放了超声波干扰器，
I put an ultrasonic jammer on the audio,
但摄像机还是能看到我们。
but the cameras can still see us.
听着，我会带你离开这里，
Look, I'm gonna get you out of here,
但这需要一些时间。
but it's gonna take some time.
时间是我所没有的。
Time is what I don't have.
我得回去找多姆。
I need to get back to Dom.
我在这个笼子里对谁都没用。
I'm no good to anyone in this cage.
我有一种感觉，你大老远跑来可不是没有计划的。
I have a feeling you didn't come all this way without a plan.
游戏识别游戏。
Game recognizes game.
如果我走了这一步，就没有回头路了。
If I make this move, there's no coming back.
我已经喜欢上它了。
I like it already.
好吧。首先，让我们把你弄出这个牢房。
Okay. First, let's get you out of this cell.
-会疼的。——嗯?
- It's gonna hurt. - Hmm?
-跟我合作。
- Work with me.
开门!
Open the door!
-推倒它!
- Knock it down!
卫兵!卫兵!
Guards! Guards!
——帮助!-放开她!
-  Help! - Let her go!
-放开她!
- Let her go!
真的吗?
Really?
♬是的，是的，是的
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
♬你在某地，某地，某地，就像一辆火车头
♪ Yo soy loca, loca, loca, like a locomotive ♪
♬来自一个肮脏的钱是唯一动机的地方
♪ Come from a place where dirty money is the only motive ♪
永远不要让任何人告诉我如何生活
♪ Never let nobody tell me how to live mi vida ♪
♬骑洋车那么快，叫不上我♬
♪ Riding foreigns so fast, calling no me toca ♪
♬让他们见鬼去吧，为什么我的中间名是"toma"
♪ I'm-a give 'em hell, why my middle name is "toma" ♪
♬昵称是古柯，然后他们就想看我不穿裤子的样子
♪ Nickname coca, then they wanna see me with no ropas ♪
♬给他们，直到他们尖叫，“不más”
♪ Give it to them till they screaming, "No más" ♪
♬是的，是的，是的。
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah.
♬我喜欢你cómo我喜欢你♬
♪ Se preguntan que cómo lo hago ♪
♬Los ojos costa, las baby escotadas♬
♪ Los ojos costa, las babys escotadas ♪
♬我的公寓很漂亮，但我不喜欢你
♪ Y los aparatos encima por si nos vamos ♪
♬Suelta, la baby est Suelta♪
♪ Suelta, la baby está suelta... ♪
是surpresa !
Que surpresa!
看看这个。
Look at this.
没有你，这一切都不会发生。
None of this happens without you.
欢迎回家。很高兴见到你，兄弟。
Welcome home. Good to see you, bro.
迪奥戈，很高兴见到你。
Diogo, good to see you.
啊。看看你。
Ah. Look at you.
我听说你被人盯上了。
So, uh, I hear you got a little heat on you.
不，我只是在找人。
Nah, I'm just looking for someone.
我们能帮什么忙?
How can we help?
你已经说过了。
You already did.
我需要你见个人。一只山羊。
I need you to meet somebody. A GOAT.
一个活生生的传奇。
A living legend, literally.
今晚你一定是赢家了。
You must be in the winner's circle tonight.
我看到你在里面放了RB26，对吧?
I see you put in a RB26 in that, right?
L24可承受不了这么大的推力。
L24 would never handle this much boost.
我家乡的儿子会同意的。
My boy back home would approve.
我不是在寻求任何人的认可。
I'm not looking for anyone's approval.
在你超越自己之前，看看你的周围。
Before you get ahead of yourself, look around you.
我们都在寻求一点认同。
We're all looking for a little validation.
-你要参加比赛吗?
- You racing or what?
相信我，你不会想抽烟的。
Trust me, you don't want that smoke.
我今晚不是来被解雇的。
I'm not here for pink slips tonight.
-你和这里的所有人。
- You and everyone here.
是啊!
Yeah!
谁能打败我，就给他一百万美元。
A million dollars for whoever can beat me.
•迪奥戈时,在这里。
Diogo, here.
是的。
Yes.
伊莎贝尔。
Isabel.
今晚有比赛，是吗?
There will be a race tonight, yes?
是的,也许吧。
Yeah, maybe.
-拜托，我在上面。
- Pretty please, with me on top.
多米尼克Toretto。
Dominic Toretto.
我就知道你会来找我。
I knew you would come for me.
很抱歉我们没能在罗马见面。
I'm sorry we didn't get to meet in Roma.
我们都很忙。
We were both so busy.
我是但丁。 很高兴认识你。
I'm Dante. Enchanté.
你是fantástico, fabuloso, o cara.
And you were fantástico, fabuloso, o cara.
他拯救了梵蒂冈。
He saved the Vatican.
谁会这么做?
Who does that?
认真对待。教皇吗?上帝吗?
Seriously. The Pope? God?
对了，你看到我刚才做的了吗?
By the way, did you see what I did there?
穿过城市的球是
The ball through the city was
向我家的保险箱致敬。
a bit of an homage to my family's safe.
除了它着火了。
Except it was on fire.
你还记得我父亲吗?
You remember my father?
——埃尔南·雷耶斯——是的。
- Hernan Reyes. - Yes.
我记得他以为他已经掌控了这座城市。
I remember he thought he had his foot on this city's neck.
但你知道发生了什么吗?
But you know what happened?
我把他打倒了。
I took him down.
我们不要在孩子们面前争吵。
Let's not argue in front of the children.
你完全正确。
You are absolutely right.
我父亲是个可怕的人
My father was a horrible man,
非常坏的爸爸，
very bad daddy,
但我挺喜欢他的
but I kind of liked him.
你偷了我们的钱就把他从我身边夺走了
And you took him from me when you stole our money
留给我们的只有痛苦。
and left us with nothing but suffering.
我就是为这个来的。
Well, that's what I came here for.
结束这种痛苦。
To end that suffering.
对了，我没拿那笔钱。
Oh, and I didn't take that money.
我把它烧了。
I burned it.
哦。
Uh-oh.
巴西是我的，
Well, Brazil is mine,
这座城市是我的
and I own this city.
哦。
Ooh.
你们以为什么都能买到。
You people think you can buy everything.
但你买不到街道。
But you can't buy the streets.
我们支持多姆。
We stand with Dom.
这太尴尬了。
Well, this is awkward.
所以，不如我们开始互相射击吧
So, how about we all just start shooting each other
看看会发生什么?
and see what happens?
或者我们赛跑。
Or we race.
如果你赢了，就带我进去。
If you win, you take me in.
如果你输了……
If you lose...
不要失去。
Don't lose.
你们都来是因为想看比赛。
You all came 'cause you wanted to see a race.
让我们比赛!
Let's race!
♬Somos de la street, zona precaución♬
♪ Somos de la street, zona precaución ♪
♬节日快乐mí，你会快乐campeón♬
♪ La fiesta pa' mí, yo soy el campeón ♪
♬Pasame otro gallo
♪ Pasame otro gallo
♬Pasame otro caguamón, pero dime que♬
♪ Pasame otro caguamón, pero dime que ♪
♬派对，派对，派对，派对，派对，派对
♪ Party, party, party, party, party, party, party ♪
♬你爱我的爸爸，你爱我的爸爸
♪ Yo la rompo como daddy, yo la rompo como daddy ♪
哎哟，哎哟，哎哟，哎哟，哎哟，哎哟
♪ Ahora dice que yo soy su zaddy, zaddy, zaddy, zaddy ♪
♬天狗，天狗，钱，我想要你爸爸♬
♪ Tengo paca, tengo money, me puedes llamar your daddy ♪
♬哦，耶，哦，耶…
♪ Ooh, yeah, ooh, yeah...
哎哟。
Ouch.
哦。
Ooh.
黑色配黑色看起来不错。
Black on black look good.
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking,
是的，地毯和窗帘很相配。
and, yes, the carpet matches the drapes.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
真不敢相信我要和伟大的多米尼克·托雷托比赛了。
I can't believe I'm gonna race the great Dominic Toretto.
我很紧张。
I have butterflies.
你真是令人印象深刻。
You're just so impressive.
你赢了那么多比赛。
You've won so many races.
每个人都爱你。
Everyone loves you.
你救了那么多人的命。
You've saved so many lives.
我知道。
I know.
就像你是个…
It's like you're a...
一个圣人。
a saint.
圣多米尼克。
Saint Dominic.
我一直在研究你。
And I've been studying you.
看着你。
And watching you.
我想不明白。
I can't figure it out.
如何……
How...
你如何选择?
How do you choose?
你如何选择你要保存的?
How do you choose the ones you save?
老爹Yankee Myke Towers演奏]
" by Daddy Yankee Myke Towers playing]
♬我爱你，我爱你
♪ A ella le gusta la gasolina
♬Dame más汽油…
♪ Dame más gasolina...
Cheguei。
Cheguei.
♬我爱你，我爱你，我爱你
♪ Ando siempre en alta velocidad violando la ley ♪
♬我爱你，我爱你
♪ Todo el mundo que abra camino ♪
♬你的传奇是什么
♪ Que va llegando el rey
♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Se quedan atrás, yo acelero no nos dieron break... ♪
♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Vroom, vroom, el que tenga algo que aporte... ♪
雅虎
Yahoo!
♬不，我爱你，我爱你，我爱你
♪ No me hagan sacar a la maquina del garaje ♪
♬Rápido y furioso no me pidan que le baje♬
♪ Rápido y furioso no me pidan que le baje ♪
♬Prendan fuego和los mores de alto caballaje…♪
♪ Prendan fuego a los motores de alto caballaje... ♪
是啊!
Yeah!
♬Prendan fuego和los mores de alto caballaje♬
♪ Prendan fuego a los motores de alto caballaje ♪
♬Rápido y furioso, rápido y furioso♬
♪ Rápido y furioso, rápido y furioso ♪
♬Prendan fuego和los mores de alto caballaje…♪
♪ Prendan fuego a los motores de alto caballaje... ♪
我要打败你了，宝贝!
I'm beating you, baby!
哦。
Oh.
你太急切了。
You're too eager.
这就是我说的!
That's what I'm talking about!
哦，不，不，不，不，不，不。你不应该那样做。
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. You shouldn't do that.
多米尼克，你会选谁?
Dominic, who will you choose?
你会选谁，多姆?
Who you gonna choose, Dom?
你会救她吗?
Are you gonna save her?
-还是你要去救他?-走吧，宝贝!
- Or are you gonna save him? - Let's go, baby!
这场比赛是我的!
This race is mine!
喵，喵，喵……
Eeny, meeny, miny...
看来你已经做出了选择。
Looks like you made your choice.
终于!哇!
Finally! Whoo!
哦，不，迪奥戈!
Oh, no, Diogo!
技巧的问题。每个人都死了。
Trick question. Everyone dies.
一、二、三。
And one, two, three.
——繁荣!
- Boom!
是啊!
Yeah!
我赢了，宝贝!
I win, baby!
继续来，多姆!
Keep coming, Dom!
有那么多的乐趣可以享受!
There's so much more fun to be had!
来吧。
Come on.
早上好，阳光。
Good morning, sunshine.
该死的。
Goddamn it.
然后他就像，“轰!"
And then he was like, "Boom!"
我就像，“砰!”她说:“什么?"
And I was like, "Blam!" And she was like, "What?"
我当时说:“闭嘴。”
I was like, "Shut up."
现在我是世界上最好的赛车手了，所以…
And now I'm the best racer in the world, so...
别碰那个。让它晾干。
Do not touch that. Let it dry.
你们看起来棒极了。
You guys look fantastic.
我知道黑色很显瘦也很吓人，
I know the black is very slimming and very scary,
但是粉彩，你知道，它们是当季的，
but the pastels, you know, they're in season,
我觉得它淡化了一点男子气概，
and I feel like it tones down the masculinity a little bit,
这是我们现在需要的。
which we all need these days.
你知道吗?
Did you know...
听我说。
Listen to me.
你知道我在法律上已经死了两分钟吗?
Did you know that I was legally dead for two minutes?
两分钟。
Two minutes.
-鲍勃，注意听。
- Bob, pay attention.
你知道我看到了什么吗?
And you know what I saw?
什么都没有。
Nothing.
什么都不是。
Not a goddamn thing.
但我觉得一旦他…
But I do feel like once he, uh...
打碎了我的头骨，也打开了我的思维。
cracked my skull open, it just opened my mind.
是啊，很深，对吧?
Yeah, that's deep, right?
-你说得对，鲍勃。
- You're absolutely right, Bob.
我们该回去工作了。
We should get back to work.
真是个固执的人。
Such a stickler.
好吧。(叹气)让我想想。
All right. [sighs] Let's see.
我们应该拿走他们所有的钱吗?
Should we take all their money?
你。你是邪恶的。
You. You are evil.
-谢谢你的聆听。
- Thank you for listening.
因此，mi casa, su casa。
So, mi casa, su casa.
等这些干了，喝完这些莫吉托，
Let these dry, finish those mojitos,
很快就会有人来把你们埋了。
and, um, someone's gonna come and bury you guys soon.
我要去洗头了。
I'm gonna go wash my hair.
现在，在我年轻的时候，我曾经炫耀一个蓬松的♬
♪ Now, in my younger days, I used to sport a shag ♪
♬当我上学的时候，我把午餐放在书包里
♪ When I went to school, I carried lunch in a bag ♪
♬给老师一个苹果，因为我知道我会得到一个吻
♪ With an apple for my teacher 'cause I knew I'd get a kiss ♪
♬下课的时候总是很生气……♪
♪ Always got mad when the class was dismissed... ♪
不。
No.
——什么?
- What?
好吧。
All right.
哇。
Whoa.
酷。那是什么?
Cool. What is that?
这是一个技术工具包。
That's a technical tool kit.
别担心，这只是一堆很棒的东西
Don't worry, it's just a bunch of awesome stuff
你永远都用不上的。
that you're never gonna get to use.
——好的。
- Okay.
眼睛睁开。静静不动。
Eyes open. Hold still.
别那样笑。
Don't smile like that.
-真让人不安。
- It's unsettling.
甜的。你的新名字是切斯特…
Sweet. Your new name is Chester...
切斯特?-…和你一起划独木舟
Chester? -...and you're on a kayaking trip with
-你的帅哥，
- your handsome,
罗杰叔叔大声说。
ripped Uncle Roger.
好吧。
All right.
现在，该给你买些新衣服了。
Now, time to get you some new clothes.
你知道的，比
You know, something a little more chic than
穿睡衣，好吗?
pj pants, all right?
-从加油站?-从加油站。
- From a gas station? - From a gas station.
你看，我就是不明白。
See, I just don't understand.
中情局为什么要背弃我们，
Why would the agency turn they backs on us,
我们为他们做了那么多?
after all we've done for them?
那个疯子把一切都推到我们头上，
That madman pinned it all on us,
现在我们成了头号公敌。
and now we're public enemy number one.
多姆会在集合点和我们碰面。
Well, Dom is gonna meet us at the rendezvous point.
但与此同时，我们得保持低调。
But in the meantime, we have to stay under the radar.
我们要做好战斗的准备。
And we got to get ready to fight.
等等，所以我们需要枪，大炮，坦克?
Wait, so we need guns, artillery, tanks?
是啊，但我们没钱怎么去买啊?
Yeah, but how are we gonna get that with no money?
怎么啦？
What?
-我们被黑了。
- We've been hacked.
看。每一个帐户。
Look. Every account.
我们过去20年赚的每一块钱都没了。
Every dollar we made over the last 20 years is gone.
他拿走了一切。
He took everything.
我们在抢劫的时候被抢劫了。
We got heisted during our own heist.
-只要解密…是的。-解密区块链。
- Just decrypt the... Yeah. - Decrypt the blockchain.
我这就去。然后我们可以找到事务哈希值。
I'm on it. Then we can find the transaction hash.
事务哈希值。
The transaction hash.
获取接收ip。完全正确。
Gets us the receiving IPs. Exactly.
英语。
English.
跟着我们的钱走，天才。
Following our money, genius.
我们在查他寄到哪里去了。
We're trying to see where he sent it.
编码是下一个层次。
The coding is next-level.
我从来没见过这样的事。
I've never seen anything like this.
我们需要更多的计算能力。
We need more computing power.
如果我们破产了要怎么做?
How are we gonna do that if we broke?
你说"我们"破产是什么意思?
What do you mean, "we" broke?
等等，你还瞒着我们?
Wait, you holding out on us?
难怪你一直这么冷静。
No wonder you've been so calm.
兄弟，你以为这是什么，兄弟?
Bro, what-what d-- what do you think this is, bro?
你知道吗?转身。
You know what? Turn around.
“转身”?你…
"Turn around"? What do you...
你说"转身"是什么意思?
What you mean, "turn around"?
伙计，我是个成年人了……
Man, I'm a grown-ass...
-什么，你在干什么?罗曼，别这样。
- What-- N-- What are you doing? Hey, Roman, do not.
别告诉我你穿的是塑身衣。
Please tell me you're not wearing Spanx.
哦，这不是塑身衣。这些银行。
Oh, this ain't Spanx. These banks.
不过没关系，兄弟。我抓住你了。
But it's okay, bro. I got you.
好吧?
All right?
你懂我的意思吗?
You know what I mean?
是的。这是给你的。
Yeah. That's for you.
这是给你的。
That's for you.
让我看看。
Let me see.
阿憨，你总是很擅长拿包，
Han, you always good for the bag,
因为包总是会回来的，你知道的。
'cause the bag always come back, you know.
所以我需要你们所有人的收据。
So what I need from all of y'all, I need receipts.
你在跟谁说话?收到你的收据了。
Who is you talking to? Got your receipt.
那我们去哪里网购呢?
So where do we go to shop off the grid?
我知道一个地方。
I know a place.
等待。中情局在追杀我们。他们不会看到我们的脸吗?
Wait. The agency's after us. Aren't they gonna see our faces?
是的，我正指望着呢。
Yeah, I'm counting on it.
谍报术的第一条规则:
The first rule of tradecraft:
如果他们找不到你，你就不会失去一个尾巴。
you can't lose a tail if they don't find you.
-哦，对不起。——对不起。
- Oh, sorry. - Sorry.
我就——等等。你知道吗，我只是…
I'll just-- Wait. You know what, I'm just...
我们只是，如果你想走，那就走吧。
We'll just-- If you want to, uh, go.
我们就待在这里。
Uh, we'll stay here.
-你们，你们绕过去。-绕过去?太好了。
- You guys, you guys go around. - Go around? Great.
转动。
Go around.
先生，我们刚找到那个男孩和他叔叔的线索。
Sir, we just got a hit on the boy and his uncle.
其他队员还在欧洲。
The rest of the team is still in Europe.
我们正在和当地政府联系。
We're interfacing with local authorities.
忘记当局。
Forget authorities.
这些人一直在逃避警察的追捕
These people have been outrunning the cops
因为他们能踩到油门踏板。
since they could reach the gas pedal.
通知每一个告密者，走私者，
Get word to every snitch, smuggler,
最厉害的杀手和黑客。
hitter and hacker we've ever used.
有钱能使鬼推磨，人也能。
Money talks and so will they.
-我们收到了警报
- We're getting an alert
在黑场A。
on Black Site A.
苔丝刚去看了奥尔蒂斯。
Tess just visited Ortiz.
他们聊得愉快吗?
They have a nice chat?
猜不是。
Guess not.
帮我倒回去。
Run it back for me.
停止。放大。
Stop. Zoom in.
追踪她的飞行路线。
Back-trace her flight path.
找出她之前在哪里。
Find out where she was before this.
那就是Dom所在的地方。
That's where Dom is.
你一直都知道我是谁，对吧?
You knew who I was all along, didn't you?
从我见到你的那一刻起。
From the moment I saw you.
你妹妹用她的眼睛微笑，用她的心引导。
Your sister smiled with her eyes and led with her heart.
就像你一样。
Just like you do.
我们一点也不像。
We were nothing alike.
她是个好姐姐。
She was the good sister.
总是把别人放在第一位。
Always putting others first.
总是做正确的事。
Always doing what was right.
有时我会想死错了人。
Sometimes I would think that the wrong sister died.
为什么是好人，而不是我?
Why the good one and not me?
你说自己一点都不像她，你错了。
You're wrong about not being anything like her.
你觉得这是她想听的吗?
You think that's what she wants to hear?
一个警察和一个街头赛车手。
A cop and a street racer.
我告诉你一件事。
I'll tell you something.
他们在同一条路上走了足够长的时间……
They travel down the same road long enough...
…他们意识到他们是多么的相似。
...and they realize how much alike they really are.
相信我……
Trust me...
…我知道。
...I know.
她还在做这件事，不是吗?
She's still doing it, isn't she?
她还在帮助别人。
She's still helping people.
她在帮助我们。
She's helping us.
你知道吗，埃琳娜
You know, Elena,
她知道雷耶斯一家的一切。
she knew everything about the Reyes family.
在他们杀了她丈夫之后
After they killed her husband,
她一生都在努力扳倒他们。
she dedicated her life trying to take them down.
我想我还有她的文件。
I think I still have her files.
等等，所以我们要找到军用装备
Wait, so we gonna find military-grade gear
在伦敦市中心?
in the middle of London?
你说你想在网上购物。
You said you wanted to shop off the grid.
等一下。我们刚才是时间旅行吗?
Wait a second. Did we just time-travel?
你会找黑市交易吗
Would you look for a black-market operation
在这样的地方?
in a place like this?
你有邮件。
You've got mail.
-哦，零食。-给我收据，伙计
- Ooh, snacks. - Get me a receipt, homey.
我怎么能从自动售货机拿到收据呢?
How am I gonna get a receipt from a vending machine?
你自己想办法怎么样?
How about you figure it out?
书面记录，兄弟。用于税务注销。
Paper trail, bruh. For tax write-off.
我向上帝发誓……
I swear to God...
怎么了，Bowie420?
What's up, Bowie420?
哦,狗屎。FreddieMerc吗?
Oh, shit. FreddieMerc?
怎么啦？在你认识我之前，我也有自己的生活。
What? I had a life before you knew me.
鲍伊经营着最臭名昭著的
Bowie here runs one of the most notorious
网上黑市。
online black markets.
如果你想要，他会卖的。
If you want it, he'll sell it.
我还以为你不喜欢我这点呢。
I thought you didn't like that about me, though.
嗯，绝望的时刻。
Well, desperate times.
这是哪种松饼?
What kind of muffins are these?
哦，那些松饼真有趣。
Oh, those are fun muffins.
你有四个孩子，
You have like four of them,
你会穿着内衣看《幻想曲》。
you'll be in your underwear watching Fantasia.
你们就是为这个来的吗?我的松饼吗?
Is that what you guys came for? My muffins?
要开个松饼派对吗?
Oh, it's gonna be a muffin party?
我们，我们需要交通工具。
We, uh, we need transport.
武器，汽车，工程。
Weapons, cars, the works.
和安静。
And quietly.
好吧，那我只需要现金。好吧?
Cool, then I'm just gonna need cash. Okay?
没有密码之类的东西。
None of that crypto stuff.
黑杰夫·贝佐斯帮你搞定了。
Oh, the Black Jeff Bezos here got you covered.
黑色的贝佐斯?-是的，他甚至去过外太空。
Black Bezos? -Yeah, he's even been into outer space.
哇。-如果你们要把我的钱给我，
Wow. -If y'all was gonna be giving out my money,
我希望你能提醒我一下，
I'd appreciate some type of a heads-up,
你知道我在说什么吗?
you know what I'm saying?
我们谈多少钱，兄弟?
How much we talking about, bruh?
只是一个合理的数量。
Just like a reasonable amount.
怎么样?
How about that?
这些钱都不够买松饼。
That won't even cover the muffins.
这家伙是认真的吗?
Is this guy serious?
狗屎的疯狂。Mm-kay。
Shit's crazy. Mm-kay.
拜托，伙计，你是宇航员。
Come on, man, you're an astronaut.
嗯，这个怎么样?
Well, how about that?
怎么，你把钱都留在太空了吗?
What, did you leave all your money in space?
伙计，把这个给我。
Man, give me this.
-谢谢。-你是认真的吗?
- Thank you. - Are you serious right now?
你知道这里的一切都是我付的吧?
You know I pay for everything around here, right?
你应该支付所有的费用。
You should pay for everything.
正是你在罗马的任务让我们来到这里。
It's your mission in Rome that got us here in the first place.
不，是你的情报把我们带到了罗马。
No, it was your intel that led us to Rome.
公平地说，这种设置会让我们中的大多数人感到困惑。
To be fair, that setup would have confused the best of us.
不，我受够了。
No, I'm tired of this.
因为他只会说话。
'Cause all he do is talk.
然后每个人都要做好自己和你的工作。
And then everyone has to do their job and yours.
你在说什么，泰吉?
What are you saying, Tej?
-我在说什么?嘿,家伙。
- Mean, what I'm saying? Hey, guys.
-这是一个家庭环境。——什么?真的吗?
- This is a family environment. - What? Really?
——真的吗?出去吧，伙计们。
- Really? Take it outside, fellas.
我们在做什么，兄弟?
So, what we doing, bruh?
哦。
Uh-oh.
-先生们，拜托!伙计们!
- Gentlemen, please! Guys!
哦，不是自动售货机。不。女人:难以置信。
Oh, not the vending machine. No. -WOMAN: Unbelievable.
伙计们，你们造成了几十美元的损失!
Guys, you're causing like dozens of dollars in damage!
我们走吧。来吧。
Let's go. Come on.
我们应该停止这一切吗?
Should we stop this?
坚持住!-不，让他们团结起来。
Hold on! - Nah, let 'em bond.
嘿!那台电脑是98年的!
Hey! That computer's from, like, '98!
嗯?
Huh?
鲍伊(呼应):怎么回事，伙计?
BOWIE [echoing]: What the hell, man?
好吧。好吧。
Okay. All right.
我们现在在做胃。
We doing stomachs now.
好了好了，够了。
All right, all right, that's enough.
你想要这个已经很多年了!呃，我想
You've been wanting that for years! -BOWIE: Uh, I think
他把复印机弄坏了，现在还能用。
he hit the copy machine so hard it works now.
那是什么鬼东西?
What the hell was that?
他就像一个贫民窟的魔术师。
He's like a ghetto magician.
你知道这是什么，兄弟。
You know what it is, bruh.
-我揍你-你刚揍我?
- I beat your ass. - You just beat my ass?
-揍我一顿?-天啊，
- Beat my ass, huh? - My God,
你们俩能不能别吵了?请。
will you two just quit it? Please.
我们没时间了。你。
We don't have time for this. You.
-开始工作。-我只是需要
- Get to work. - Oh, I just need
黑进市场。只需要一点时间。
to hack into the marketplace. It'll just take a second.
哦。
Oops.
怎么回事，鲍伊?你刚刚做了什么?
What the hell, Bowie? What did you just do?
我很抱歉。你们的脸是，
I'm sorry. Your guys's faces are,
在暗网上到处都是。
like, all over the dark web.
我是说，那奖励太棒了。
I mean, that reward is dope.
-噢。嘿。-我们得走了。
-  Ow. Hey. - We have to move.
-还有几分钟就到。-听着，这不是针对你
- The agency's minutes away. - Look, it's nothing personal.
-嘿，有趣的松饼请我，好吗?——什么?嗯?
- Hey, fun muffins on me, okay? - What? Huh?
——哦!哦!
- Oh! Oh!
我活该。
I deserved that.
-你没事吧，兄弟?-是的，谢谢你，伙计。
- Are you okay, bro? - Yeah, thank you, man.
好吧，那你现在要去哪?
All right, so where to now, huh?
——监狱?
- Jail?
我知道某个地方。我最不想去的地方。
I know somewhere. Last place I want to go.
站在我这边是什么感觉?
How does it feel to be on my side of the law?
他们喜欢在弄坏东西之前先修好。
They like to fix things before they break 'em.
那是个恶心的地方，蕾蒂。
It's a sick place, Letty.
不客气
You're welcome.
你做了什么?
What did you do?
我把麻醉气体引入了他们的空调。
I rerouted anesthetic gas into their air conditioning.
我在摄像头复位前给我们争取了几分钟
And I bought us a few minutes before these cameras reset
他们发现这个地方变成了睡眠研究中心。
and they find out this place turned into a sleep study.
你是想继续生气，还是想离开这里?
You gonna stay grumpy or do you want to get out of here?
他们不会永远睡下去的。
They're not gonna sleep forever.
你不想回到你亲爱的家人身边吗?
Don't you want to get back to your precious family?
大便。
Shit.
看来你已经搞定了。
Seems like you got this covered.
-你需要我做什么?-我有个计划
- What do you need me for? - I have a plan,
但这是两个人的工作。
but it's a two-person job.
那么，这有那么难吗?
Now, was that so hard?
我们还有多少时间?
How much time do we have?
我想大概四分钟吧。
I'd say about four minutes.
只能这样了。
It'll have to do.
♬那我就像斯伯丁一样
♪ Then I ball like Spalding
♬不能揭穿我的虚张声势，当…我的使命是…♪
♪ Can't call my bluff when the ... is my calling... ♪
♬我让他们疯狂
♪ I got 'em going crazy
♪啊!
♪ Huh!
如果我是你，我就待在下面。
I'd stay down if I was you.
你得再狠狠揍我一顿。
You got to hit me harder for that.
你会后悔的。
You're gonna regret this.
♬那我就像斯伯丁一样
♪ Then I ball like Spalding
♬不能揭穿我的虚张声势，当…♬是我的呼唤
♪ Can't call my bluff when the ... is my calling ♪
♬全力以赴
♪ All in
♬这是崭新的一天，新的步伐，轻轻的慢跑……♪
♪ It's a brand-new day, new pace, light jogging... ♪
-♬哈!♬我让他们发疯了
- ♪ Huh! - ♪ I got 'em going crazy
♪啊!
♪ Huh!
♬我让他们疯狂
♪ I got 'em going crazy
♬所有这些讨厌…别唬我……♪
♪ All these hating ... don't phase me... ♪
-♬疯了-♬哼!
- ♪ Crazy - ♪ Huh!
♬这些都不是…你要把我逼疯……♪
♪ None of these ... gon' phase me... ♪
♪啊!哈!
♪ Huh! Huh!
♬气得像德士古
♪ Gassed like a Texaco
♬我是说，一个…离岸就像我是墨西哥
♪ I mean, a ... offshore like I'm Mexico ♪
♬如果你…不确定，我可以让你知道
♪ And if a ... unsure, I can let ya know ♪
♬我的意思是，我像小数点一样坚守着这一点
♪ I mean, I stick to the point like a decimal ♪
♪啊!
♪ Huh!
♬我让他们疯狂。
♪ I got 'em going crazy.
但丁雷耶斯。
Dante Reyes.
出生于葡萄牙。
Born in Portugal.
母亲来自太平洋群岛。
Mother from the Pacific Islands.
从小就有反社会倾向。
Sociopathic tendencies from an early age.
他从少管所到监狱再到精神病院。
He bounced from juvie to prison to mental wards.
每次，爸爸都会把他抱出来。
And each time, Daddy was there to spring him out.
他父亲死后，他就消失了。
After his father died, he disappeared.
雷耶斯死前拥有的房产
Properties Reyes owned before he died.
现在都卖了又买回来了。
Now all sold and repo'd.
除了这个。
Except this one.
警察局。
The police station.
它已经被遗弃多年了。
It's been abandoned for years.
猜猜房契上是谁的名字。
And guess whose name is on the deed.
但丁雷耶斯。
Dante Reyes.
我会在那里找到答案的。
I'll find my answer there.
我和你一起去。
I'm coming with you.
我要你保证安全。
I need you to stay safe.
我就能赢那场比赛了。
I would have won that race, you know.
所以你想重赛?
So you want a rematch?
-这是我的要求。
- I'm demanding it.
我想我们很快就会见到你了。
So I guess I'll see you soon.
伙计们，你们不会想这么做的。
Guys, you don't want to do this.
他需要一块新表，警察。
He needs a new watch, cop.
瞧，这块表是别人送的。
Look, the watch was a gift.
但我的护裆里有16克拉未切割的钻石
But I got 16 carats of uncut diamonds in my jockstrap
如果你想看的话。
if you want to take a look.
现在你真的需要一块新表了。
Now you really do need a new watch.
该死的。
Damn it.
B，你没事吧?
B, you okay?
试过口香糖吗?口香糖有帮助。
Tried gum? Gum helps.
我不喜欢飞机。
I don't like planes.
如果是身高的问题，那就有问题了。
If it's the height, that's gonna be an issue.
你知道吗，我以前很怕车。
You know, I used to be scared of cars.
我爸爸死后，我想我是在自责。
After my dad died, I guess I blamed myself.
这很艰难。
It was tough.
我一直都有恐慌症。
I had panic attacks, the whole bit.
见鬼，我坐公共汽车。
Heck, I took the bus.
是的。我想我只是太担心犯错误了
Yeah. I think I was just so worried about making mistakes
而且不如我哥哥好。
and not being as good as my brother.
——你呢?-不好意思。
- You? - Uh, excuse me.
你见过你爸爸吗?
Have you met your dad?
他的影子相当大。
He casts a pretty big shadow.
嗯。感觉好点了吗?
Huh. Feeling better?
-是的。——好。
- Yeah. - Good.
我也是。
Me, too.
先生，这是您点的饮料。
Here's the drink that you ordered, sir.
你认识她?
You know her?
是啊，有身居高位的朋友真好。
Yeah, it's good to have friends in high places.
我数到三，
On the count of three,
我们要起来去趟洗手间。准备好了吗?
we're gonna get up and go to the bathroom. Ready?
——三个。
- Three.
那些人是谁?
Who were those guys?
机构。他们找到我们了。现在让我们丢掉尾巴。
Agency. They found us. Now let's lose our tail.
圣史……
Holy shi...
等等!只对歌词和脚趾说脏话。
Wait! Swearing is for song lyrics only and stubbed toes.
忘了它吧。注意。
Forget about it. Pay attention.
好吧?我们飞得太高了，不能滑翔，
Okay? We're-we're too high to glide,
所以我们需要推力，也就是说，
so we need thrust, which means, uh,
燃烧，这意味着…?
combustion, which means...?
氧气和燃料。
Oxygen and fuel.
酒精。
Alcohol.
——嗯…——嗯?
- Um... - Huh?
哦。
Oh.
这是玫瑰。没用的。
That's rosé. Not gonna work.
很长的故事。但是很好的主动性。
Long story. But good initiative.
我很高兴不是因为它的高度。
I'm glad it wasn't the height.
享受旅程吧，小B。
Enjoy the ride, Little B.
鲍伊给我们做了标记。
Bowie tagged us.
中情局在跟踪我们。
The agency is on our tail.
我们得找到装备
We need to find gear
尽快赶到集合地点。
and get to the rendezvous as soon as possible.
就在这里。
It's right here.
你们退后。让我来处理这个。
You guys hold back. Let me take care of this.
不，不，不。这不是个好主意。
No, no, no. Th-That's a bad idea.
-我是说罗马式的糟糕。——什么?
- I mean like Roman-level bad. - What?
你在说什么，伙计?
What are you talking about, man?
你听到我说的了。
You heard what I said.
听着，兄弟，你没必要这么做。
Look, bro, you don't have to do this, man.
你知道我挺你的。
You know I got your back.
我们支持你。
We got your back.
-我得一个人去。
- I got to do this alone.
我有事要跟你说。
I have something to talk to you about.
死人出现在我门前的唯一原因是
The only reason a dead guy shows up at my door:
报复。
revenge.
哦,史…
Oh, shi...
-该死。——大便。汉!
- Oh, shit. - Shit. Han!
我应该死的。
Should have stayed dead.
我能进去。我能进去。
I can get in. I can get in.
我不喜欢重复自己的话。
I don't like repeating myself.
你毁了我的零食。
You ruined my snacks.
放松。我不想和你打架。
Relax. I don't want to fight you.
那就快结束了。
Then this is gonna end quick.
你带了更多的人来杀我?
You bring more men to kill me?
他们也想杀了我。
They're trying to kill me, too.
看来我们又多了一个同伴。
Well, it looks like we got more company.
-你还开车?-你觉得呢?
- You still drive? - What do you think?
好吧，给我一点时间。
Okay, just give me a second.
冻结!
Freeze!
-放下笔记本电脑!——好的。
- Drop the laptop! - Okay.
-伙计们，我加入。
- Guys, I'm in.
不，不，不，不!
No, no, no, no!
现在我们扯平了。
Now we're even.
你没事吧?
You okay?
现在，看，这一切我都明白了。
Now, see, I understand all this.
那是什么鬼东西?
What the hell was that?
你害怕了。我看到了。
You got scared. I saw that.
-没人害怕，兄弟。-不，你…他很害怕。
- Ain't nobody got scared, bruh. - No, you were... he was scared.
莱蒂[对着发言者]:我们有一位不速之客。
LETTY [over speakers]: We have an unwanted guest.
DOM(通过扬声器):我的家人?
DOM [over speakers]: My family?
他们现在是安全的。
They're safe for now.
你什么都不怕。
You're not afraid of anything.
我不在乎死。
I don't care about dying.
我只关心保护我爱的人。
I only care about protecting the people that I love.
把我们放在你心里
Hold us in your heart
你永远不会迷失方向。
and you will never lose your way.
你什么都不怕。
You're not afraid of anything.
恐惧可以是一位伟大的老师。
Fear can be a great teacher.
小布莱恩(变形):你什么都不怕。
LITTLE BRIAN [distorted]: You're not afraid of anything.
但丁(在电话中):你觉得我住的地方怎么样?
DANTE [over phone]: How do you like my place?
我很遗憾不能带你四处看看。
I'm bummed I'm not there to show you around.
你看到我的愿景板有点尴尬。
And a little embarrassed you saw my vision board.
但至少你知道我有多努力
But at least you know how hard I've been working
让我们走到这一步。
to get us to this point.
现在我知道你死定了。
Now I know you're a dead man.
你是说复活。
You mean resurrected.
多亏了你。
Thanks to you.
你知道吗，如果你不开车的话，
You know, if you never would have gotten behind that wheel,
我永远不会成为今天的我。
I'd never be the man that I am today.
你创造了如此美好的生活
You built such a beautiful life,
充满了爱和亲情。
filled with love and family.
我从来没有这样的机会。
I never got that chance.
附带伤害，混乱，死亡。
Collateral damage, chaos, death.
这是你的遗产。
This is your legacy.
我是你的遗产。
I'm your legacy.
你知道我不明白什么吗?
You know what I can't figure out?
一个天生如此富有的人是怎么做到的
How someone born so rich
选择最穷的人生道路。
chooses the poorest path through life.
你没有荣誉可言。
You got no honor.
没有荣誉，你就没有家庭。
Without honor, you got no family.
没有家人……
And without family...
…你什么都没有。
...you've got nothing.
因为你，我一无所有。
I have nothing because of you.
我的未来。我的家人。
My future. My family.
你从我这里偷来的。
You stole that from me.
现在我要让你心碎
And now I'm gonna break yours,
一块一块地。
piece by piece.
别说话了，面对我。
Stop talking and face me.
你喜欢惊喜吗，多米?
Do you like surprises, Dommy?
我崇拜他们。
I adore them.
但游戏还没有结束。
But the game's not over yet.
还有很多人需要伤害。
There's still so many people to hurt.
我来找你。
I'm coming for you.
戴着手铐可做不到。
Well, that's gonna be hard to do in handcuffs.
好的，再见，多米。
Okay, bye, Dommy.
不，你先挂电话。
No, you hang up first.
好吧。
Okay.
Toretto,冻结。
Toretto, freeze.
是时候面对现实了，多姆。
Time to face the music, Dom.
你这是正中他下怀，警察。
You're playing right into his hands, cop.
好吧。来吧。
Okay. Come on.
哦。
Oh.
是的。
Yeah.
太好了。
Great.
就好了。
Just great.
大便。
Shit.
有点冷吗?
Little chilly?
你的计划还是很烂。
Your plan still sucks.
也许吧，但至少你会很暖和。
Maybe, but at least you'll be warm.
“谢谢你，塞弗。谢谢你。”
"Thank you, Cipher. Thank you."
-哇哦。
- Oh, wow.
看看这个。
Take a look at this.
这应该够我们齿轮部的了。
This should cover us in the gear department.
你不值得信任。
You are not to be trusted.
你也不在我的圣诞清单上。
Hey, you ain't on my Christmas list either.
这里没有免费的东西。让我把这一点说清楚。
Nothing here is for free. Let me be clear on that.
一定要他给你开收据，好吗?
Make sure you get a receipt from him, okay?
我很想看。
I'd love to see that.
我想是鲍伊吧
Well, I guess Bowie
也不是毫无价值。我可以用他的硬盘
wasn't entirely worthless. I can use his hard drive
来完成对但丁的追踪
to complete our trace of Dante.
他一直都比我们先走十步。
He's been ten moves ahead of us this whole time.
他一个人是怎么做到的?
How does he do it by himself?
这可不妙。
Uh, this isn't good.
我们的钱，分散在世界各地的账户里。
Our money, it's been split into accounts all over the world.
看看他们都登记在谁名下。
And look who they're registered to.
那些是雇佣兵杀人小队。真正的人渣。
Those are mercenary kill teams. Real scum.
他用我们的钱买了一支军队。
He used our money to buy an army.
所以这家伙不只是想让我们死。
So this guy doesn't just want us dead.
他想把我们从这个星球上抹去。
He wants to erase us off the planet.
他想拆散我们。
He's trying to tear us apart.
所以我们才需要和多姆重新连接
That's exactly why we need to link back up with Dom
在集合点。
at the rendezvous point.
你得看看这个。
You need to see this.
他们是被收买来攻击我们的
They've been paid to target us
还有之前帮助过我们的人。
and anyone who ever helped us until now.
妈妈。
Mum.
我会派交通工具等你。
I'll have transport waiting for you.
你要去哪里?
And where are you going?
我要挖几个坟墓。
I'm gonna dig some graves.
。没有人是金童，
Mr. Nobody's golden boy,
没怎么反抗就被抓住了
caught without so much as a fight.
这一点都不好玩。
That's no fun.
就像一直爬到珠穆朗玛峰一样
It's like going all the way to Everest
然后乘电梯。
and taking the elevator.
你最好系好安全带。
You might want to buckle up.
我知道你为局里做了不少好事。
I know you did some good work for the agency.
你肯定觉得这样能让你得到宽大处理。
I'm sure you figured that buys you some leniency.
但这是新的一天。
But it's a new day.
这就是现在的问题。没人听。
That's the problem nowadays. Nobody listens.
你应该少花点时间思考的
You should have spent less time with your head under the hood
还有更多的时间为即将到来的事情做准备。
and more time preparing for what's coming.
间谍已经被卫星取代，
Spies have been replaced by satellites,
战斗机飞行员靠无人机，情报靠算法。
fighter pilots by drones, intelligence by an algorithm.
一个人开车的时代
The days where one man behind the wheel of a car
都结束了，多姆。
can make a difference are over, Dom.
地狱，任何人的日子
Hell, the days of any man
后面的车轮的汽车都结束了。
behind the wheel of a car are over.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
为即将到来的事情做准备。
Preparing for what's to come.
正确的。
Right.
走了。走了。走了。
Go. Go. Go.
多米尼克，我带你回到我们第一次见面的地方。
Dominic, I brought you back to where we first met.
我给你准备了一个惊喜。
And I have a surprise for you.
Dom !
Dom!
我正在听呢。
I'm listening now.
多米尼克?
Dominic?
多米尼克!
Dominic!
你能不能别再伤害我的新朋友了?
Would you stop hurting my new friends?
不。我只是来伤害你的。
No. I'm only here to hurt you.
哦。
Oh.
我不想骗你。
I'm not gonna lie to you.
你刚才在车里表演的特技?
That little car stunt you just did?
那真是太棒了。
That was pretty awesome.
不是吗?
Wasn't it?
太酷了。
It was so cool.
但如果你不停下来
But if you don't stop,
我要把她全身都割开。
I'm gonna cut her everywhere.
得很厉害。
Badly.
她来了。
There she is.
——嗯。-时髦的迟到。
- Hmm. - Fashionably late.
你说对了。
You got me.
嗯。
Mmm.
-你走吧。
- Off you go.
家庭。
Family.
请你从我的车上下来好吗?
Will you please get off my car?
——嗯。
- Hmm.
这太不尊重了。
That is so disrespectful.
你话太多了。
You talk too much.
停,停!
Stop, stop!
你不知道自己的力量。
You don't know your own strength.
你屁眼!
You butthole!
哦,嘿。
Oh, hey.
你喜欢芭蕾吗?
Do you like ballet?
我喜欢《天鹅湖》。
I adore Swan Lake.
我觉得你更像是《胡桃夹子》里的那种人。
I feel like you're more of a-- kind of a Nutcracker guy.
一个1，一个2，还有……
And a one, and a two, and...
不!
No!
等一下。
Wait for it.
哦,不。
Oh, no.
她有危险。你会怎么做?
She's in peril. What will you do?
你知道你的问题是什么吗?
You know what your problem is?
家庭。
Family.
你不可能把他们都救出来。
You can't save 'em all.
五个四。
Five. Four.
Ah-ta-ta-ta-ta。
Ah-ta-ta-ta-ta.
继续。
Go on.
两个。
Two.
你不喜欢芭蕾。
You don't like ballet.
我能感觉到。
I can feel it.
能把上帝之眼给我吗?
May I please have the God's Eye?
-去你的。——不是吗?
- Screw you. - No?
很好吗?
Pretty please?
-哦，在这儿。
- Oh, there it is.
哦。明白了。
Ooh. Gotcha.
良好的贸易。留着车吧。
Good trade. Keep the car.
哦,Dommy !
Oh, Dommy!
我告诉过你，你欠我痛苦!
I told you, you owe me suffering!
你的遗产不是金钱或权力
Your legacy isn't money or power
或是你建立的家庭或是你过的生活。
or the family you built or the life you led.
这是你创造的生活。
It's the life you made.
还有一对父子…
And a father and his son...
就是一切。
is everything.
你在这座桥上杀了我父亲。
You killed my father on this bridge.
现在我知道去哪儿找你儿子了。
And now I know where to find your son.
很高兴认识你。
Enchanté.
你会没事的，苔丝。它完全通过了。
You're gonna be okay, Tess. It went clear through.
有点疼。
Kinda hurts.
你父亲会为你骄傲的。
Your father would be proud.
是的。
Yeah.
你会阻止他的。
You will stop him.
要有信心。
Have faith.
她需要去医院
She needs a hospital.
毫米。
Mm.
你会没事的。
You're gonna be okay.
我抓住她了。
I got her.
去救你儿子吧。
Go save your son.
我的侄子。
My nephew.
我不会道歉的，让我帮你个忙。
I'm not gonna say I'm sorry, so let me do you one better.
我们去救你儿子吧。
Let's get your son.
♬我们用开关旋转着积木，跳起来
♪ We spinnin' the block with switches, the opps out ♪
♬你曾经是帮派，你换了，你现在不是了
♪ You used to be gang, you switched, you not now ♪
如果你被困在外面，我就会跳出来
♪ Get caught outside, li'l bro 'nem gon' hop out ♪
♬不管你是不是一伙的，来看看这个弹出
♪ You gang or not, come see this pop out ♪
♬我们用开关旋转着积木，跳起来
♪ We spinnin' the block with switches, the opps out ♪
♬你曾经是帮派，你换了，你现在不是了
♪ You used to be gang, you switched, you not now ♪
如果你被困在外面，我就会跳出来
♪ Get caught outside, li'l bro 'nem gon' hop out ♪
♬不管你是不是一伙的，来看看这个弹出
♪ You gang or not, come see this pop out ♪
♬猫在岛上咆哮……♪
♪ Cat growl through the island... ♪
这里以前是一个老矿，
So, it used to be an old mine,
他们在山的深处炸了隧道。
and they blasted tunnels deep into the mountain.
我只是…
And I just, uh...
重新设计了这个地方。
repurposed the place.
你只需要对各种可能性保持开放的心态。
You just got to keep yourself open to possibilities.
当然，(叹气)你手上有很多时间。
And, of course, [sighs] have a lot of time on your hands.
你说我们在这里见他的。
You said we'd meet him here.
嘿。
Hey.
你了解你爸爸。
You know your dad.
他得保证安全。
He's got to make it safe.
我们就等着吧。
We'll just wait.
我爱你，雅各布叔叔。
I love you, Uncle Jakob.
那是什么?
What's that?
了吗?啊，我一直在做的项目。
That? Ah, project I've been working on.
你不会感兴趣的。
You wouldn't be interested.
好了，我们进入葡萄牙领空了。
All right, we're entering Portuguese airspace.
雅各布已经在那里了。多姆有消息吗?
Jakob's already there. Any word from Dom?
嘿。
Hey.
你怎么这么安静?你没事吧?
Why are you so quiet? You all right?
我就坐在这里想，伙计。
Just been sitting here thinking, man.
我就知道我闻到了烧焦的味道。
I knew I smelled something burning in here.
泰吉，这是我的任务，你们都听我的，
Tej, it was my mission, y'all took my lead,
而我却把事情搞砸了
and I messed this thing up every step of the way.
我想这整个…
I guess this whole...
我真的不适合做领导。
leadership thing really ain't for me.
你用集装箱把我们带到伦敦。
You took us to London on a container.
你花了几千美元自己的钱，
You spent thousands of dollars of your own cash,
绑在你屁股上
strapped to your ass,
现在闻起来像廉价古龙水。
that now smells like cheap cologne.
现在你坐在这里独自承担责任
Now you're sitting here taking sole responsibility
我们都穿的东西。
for something that we all wear.
是的，我知道。这听起来很愚蠢。
Yeah, I know. It sounds stupid.
不，听起来一点也不傻。
Nah, it don't sound stupid at all.
你知道这听起来像什么吗?
You know what it sounds like to me?
听起来像个领袖。
That sounds like a leader.
拜托，伙计。快起来，伙计。
Come on, man. Get your ass up, man.
我爱你，伙计。
I love you, man.
我也爱你，兄弟。
I love you, too, bro.
有时候我们得说声"对不起"
Sometimes we got to say, "I'm sorry."
我很抱歉打了你一顿，
I'm sorry for whupping your ass, man,
因为我不是故意的。
'cause I didn't really mean to do that.
整件事，就完全不一样了…-
The whole thing, it would've been a whole dif... -
-你没事吧?怎么了?
- You okay? What's wrong?
我只是对你的废话过敏。
I'm just allergic to your bullshit.
-别这样。
- Come on.
嘿，放轻松点。你会把它弄坏的。
Hey, go easy there. You're gonna break that thing.
-你没事吧?
- You all right?
上帝之眼只是用来发送
God's Eye was just used to send
数十名雇佣兵追杀多姆的儿子
dozens of mercenaries after Dom's son.
我创造的东西伤害了我们爱的人。
Something I created hurting the people we love.
这是为了帮助。
It was meant to help.
这不仅仅是但丁的事。
This is bigger than just Dante.
这不仅仅是我们的事。
This is bigger than just us.
我们必须马上阻止这个怪物。
We have to stop this monster now.
我们得走了。
We got to go.
坚持住!
Hold on!
我看到肌肉叔叔和那孩子了。
I got eyes on Uncle Muscle and the kid.
好了，大家记住计划。
All right, everybody, remember the plan.
控制和绑架。谢谢你！
Contain and kidnap. Thank you.
不。
No.
没有枪支。
No guns.
我要这个小混蛋活着。
I need this little shit alive.
至少暂时是这样。
At least for a while.
-准备好了吗?——准备好了。
- You ready? - Ready.
神圣的承宪……
Holy sh...
哦，不，你很好。你很好。
Oh, no, you're good. You're good.
好吧，歌词，脚趾和加农炮车。
Okay, uh, song lyrics, stubbed toes and cannon cars.
是的。
Yeah.
我们开始吧!
Here we go!
卡住了。卡住了。
It's stuck. It's stuck.
那里有一支军队，多姆。
They got an army down there, Dom.
你的队伍就在不远处。
Your team's not far out.
-带我们下来。-我不能把她放在这里。
- Bring us down. - I can't put her down here.
往西七公里处有个机场。
There's an airfield seven klicks west.
好的，我们在那里见。现在打开后面。
Okay, we'll meet you there. Now open the back.
多姆，真的没有地方可以降落。
Dom, there's really nowhere to land.
谁说要降落了?
Who said anything about landing?
看。
Look.
我来找你了，孩子。
I'm coming for you, son.
什么……
What the...
——爸爸!-嘿，儿子。
- Dad! - Hey, son.
很高兴见到你，大哥。
Good to see you, big bro.
很高兴见到你们。跟我去那架飞机。
Good to see you guys. Follow me to that plane.
我们就在你后面。
We're right behind you.
我抓到你了。
I got you now.
艾姆斯，我们在路上了。
Aimes, we're on our way.
多姆，我会在西边五公里处着陆。
Dom, I'll be touching down five klicks west.
但他们还在跟踪你。
But they're still on your tail.
它是卡住了。
It's jammed.
B，你在干什么?
B, what are you doing?
小心。
Careful.
好，好，好。
Okay, okay, okay.
关上前门。
Shut the front door.
小B。
Little B.
雅各布叔叔!
Uncle Jakob!
我修好了!
I fixed it!
B !
B!
Toodle-oo。
Toodle-oo.
——帮助!——Ah-ta-ta-ta-ta。闭嘴。
- Help! - Ah-ta-ta-ta-ta. Shut up.
该死的。
Damn it.
你的聚会吗?我的派对。
You party? I party.
——哇。
-  Whoa.
多姆，我跟丢了他。但丁有小B。
Dom, I lost him. Dante has Little B.
嘿,多米尼克。欢迎来到大对决。
Hey, Dominic. Welcome to the big showdown.
这是最后一圈。看看我的副驾驶。
It's the last lap. Check out my copilot.
——爸爸!-谁能料到会这样?
- Dad! - Who could've seen this coming?
我是说，除了我。
I mean, you know, except for me.
大便。看来我的油管被击中了。
Shit. Looks like my fuel line's been shot.
-我没法接近他，多姆-雅各布，坚持住。
- I can't get to him, Dom. - Jakob, stay with me.
我出局了。
I'm out of this race.
必须是你。
It has to be you.
嘿,Dom !给你个小惊喜。
Hey, Dom! Got a little surprise for you.
你养了个好儿子，多姆。
You raised a hell of a son, Dom.
是时候让我走出你的阴影了。
Time for me to step out from under your shadow.
谢谢你给我指引光明。
Thanks for showing me the light.
雅克布?
Jakob?
我要去清理一下。
I'm gonna go clear the way.
去找你儿子。
Go get your son.
雅克布,不要!
Jakob, don't!
——不!
- Don't!
雅各布叔叔!
Uncle Jakob!
看来肌肉叔叔下次烧烤不会来了。
Looks like Uncle Muscle won't be coming to the next barbecue.
哦。
Oh.
我是说，这很光荣。
I mean, it's very honorable.
三英里外。走服务路。
Three miles away. Take the service road.
它会直接带你到机场。
It'll lead you right to the airfield.
你知道怎么在街头赛车上打败你爸爸吗?
You know how to beat your dad in a street race?
把街道拿走。
Take away the streets.
——爸爸!
- Dad!
很神奇的。
Amazing.
哦。
Oh.
我们知道了。我们知道了。
We got it. We got it.
轮到我了。
My turn.
他很好。你爸爸很好。
He's good. Your dad's good.
多姆，你还有一英里。
Dom, you got one mile left.
儿子，我从不食言。
Son, I never break a promise.
现在，让我们完成驾驶课。
Now, let's finish that driving lesson.
感受一下车，
Feel the car,
找到你的路线
find your line
和飞。
and fly.
——哦!
- Oh!
——现在!
- Now!
不。
No.
现在走辅路。
Take the service road now.
-我倒了。-我们现在去找你。
- I'm wheels down. - We're headed to you now.
你的队伍已经在路上了。
Your team is on their way.
我将在机场接你。
I'll meet you at the airfield.
-你没事吧?-我很好，爸爸。
- You okay? - I'm good, Dad.
我真为你骄傲，儿子。
I'm real proud of you, son.
哦，多米小子。
Oh, Dommy boy.
很高兴再次见到你。
It's so good to see you again.
你刚才是不是用直升机撞了我?
Did you hit me with a helicopter back there?
嗯。
Hmm.
哦，你这个大畜生。我是说，我明白。
Ow, you big brute. I mean, I get it.
你在你儿子面前炫耀。
You're showing off in front of your son.
但说实话，你真的认为
But honestly, did you really think
就这么简单吗?
it was going to be that easy?
你就在我希望你在的地方。
You're exactly where I wanted you to be.
是的。
Yes.
等一下。
Wait for it.
我给你准备了一个惊喜。
I got a surprise for you.
骑兵来了。我们抓住你了，多姆。
The cavalry's here. We got you, Dom.
罗曼，离开这里。这是个陷阱。
Roman, get out of here. It's a trap.
传入的!
Incoming!
是的!
Yes!
这就是大家庭的问题所在。
See, that's the problem with having a big family.
不能保护所有人。
Can't protect 'em all.
噢!
Ooh!
多米尼克，那是你的新朋友吗?
Oh, Dominic, is that your new friend?
哦。
Aw.
你太容易预测了。
You are so predictable.
你觉得大家最后都会站在你这边吗?
You think everyone's gonna end up on your side?
问题是艾姆斯是我的先手。
Problem is Aimes was mine first.
现在工作开始了。
Now the work begins.
在那里，
And in there,
今天我们要让我们的家族走上真正的权力之路。
today we'll put our family on a path to real power.
让我们开始吧。
Let's get started.
看来我们是合伙人了
Well, looks like our partnership's
开了个好头。
off to a fantastic start.
多米尼克，要成为一个真正的圣人，
You know, Dominic, to become a real saint,
你必须创造奇迹。
you have to perform miracles.
或者以殉道者的身份死去。
Or die a martyr.
那么会是什么呢?
So what's it gonna be?
我拿走了你的钱，拿走了你的自由，
I took your money, I took your freedom,
我要带走你的家人
and I'm gonna take your family.
你会死的
And you're gonna die
知道自己救不了儿子。
knowing that you couldn't save your son.
爸爸。
Dad.
我有信心。
I have faith.
你犯了一个错误。
You made one mistake.
你从没开过我的车。
You never took my car.
哦!
Oh!
痛苦结束了，多姆。
The suffering is over, Dom.
你该去死了。
It's time for you to die.
不可能。
No way.
还觉得我的计划很烂吗?
Still think my plan sucks?
但我不会退缩
♪ But I won't back down
♬哦，哦，哦，哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh
但我不会退缩
♪ But I won't back down
♬哦，哦，哦，哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh
♬哦，耶
♪ Oh, yeah
♬现在我感到我的手在颤抖
♪ And now I feel my hands trembling ♪
♬哦，上帝
♪ Oh, Lord
♬我不能保证我会再呼吸一次
♪ Ain't no promise I'll breathe again ♪
但我不会退缩
♪ But I won't back down
♬为了我的家人，你可以赎回我♬
♪ For my family, you can ransom me ♪
♬它很难，它打破了我的膝盖
♪ Had it hard, it broke me to my knees ♪
♬在异国他乡，我开车狂怒了♬
♪ In a foreign, I'm driving furious ♪
♬就像有人在追我一样
♪ Like somebody out there after me ♪
♬我的女孩只得到了我的心
♪ My girl got my heart only
♬我的朋友们支持我，我们追逐金钱
♪ My friends they got my back, we chase money ♪
♬无论暴风雨还是晴天，我们都在一起
♪ We together when it's storm or sunny ♪
♬他们希望我让步
♪ They expect me for to back down ♪
♬这是我的命运，这可能会得到最好的我
♪ It's my destiny and this might get the best of me ♪
♬我不能让你走在我们前面
♪ I can't let you get ahead of us ♪
♬我得陪你到座位上去
♪ I'm-a have to escort you to a seat ♪
通过这一切，我们不能失败
♪ Through it all, we can't fail ♪
因为计划就是为了实现
♪ 'Cause the plan is for to achieve ♪
♬我只是真的需要一些平静
♪ I'm just really needing some peace ♪
♬希望伤痛快点离开
♪ Hoping pain quickly leave
♬我的世界已经沦陷
♪ My world has fallen
♬我要双膝跪地
♪ I'm falling to my knees
♬哦，耶
♪ Oh, yeah
♬现在我感到我的手在颤抖
♪ And now I feel my hands trembling ♪
♬哦，上帝
♪ Oh, Lord
♬我不能保证我会再呼吸一次
♪ Ain't no promise I'll breathe again ♪
但我不会退缩
♪ But I won't back down
♬哦，哦，哦，哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh
但我不会退缩
♪ But I won't back down
♬哦，哦，哦，哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh
♬哦，耶
♪ Oh, yeah
♬现在我感到我的手在颤抖
♪ And now I feel my hands trembling ♪
♬哦，上帝
♪ Oh, Lord
♬我不能保证我会再呼吸一次
♪ Ain't no promise I'll breathe again ♪
但我不会退缩
♪ But I won't back down
♬当我的手变冷
♪ And when my hands get cold
♬我只能靠自己
♪ And I'm on my own
♬我在黑暗中爬行
♪ Through the dark I crawl
♬当我的骨头感到虚弱
♪ And when my bones feel weak
♬我会继续奔跑
♪ I will keep running
♬穿过火焰
♪ Through the fire
♬我不会退缩
♪ I won't back down
♬哦，哦，哦，哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh
但我不会退缩
♪ But I won't back down
♬哦，哦，哦，哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh
♬哦，耶
♪ Oh, yeah
♬现在我感到我的手在颤抖
♪ And now I feel my hands trembling ♪
♬哦，上帝
♪ Oh, Lord
♬我不能保证我会再呼吸一次
♪ Ain't no promise I'll breathe again ♪
但我不会退缩
♪ But I won't back down
♪。
♪ Down.
保持微笑直到那一天
♪ Keep smiling until then
♬当我们在一起的时候，谁在乎云彩?♪
♪ Who cares about the clouds when we're together? ♪
♬就唱首歌，带来阳光明媚的天气
♪ Just sing a song and bring the sunny weather ♪
♬快乐的小径
♪ Happy trails
-献给你
- ♪ To you
♬直到我们再次相遇
♪ Till we meet again
但丁(在电话中):你好，搭档。
DANTE [over phone]: Howdy, partner.
你喜欢惊喜吗?
Do you like surprises?
你做了些卑鄙龌龊的事，警长。
You've done some dastardly, dirty deeds, Sheriff.
你夺走了我生命中最重要的东西。
You took the most important thing in my life from me.
Dom开车。
Dom drove the car.
-但是你… -帮帮我。
- But you... -  Help me.
…你扣动了扳机。
...you pulled the trigger.
现在我要让你受苦。
And now I'm gonna make you suffer.
♬我们又见面了
♪ We meet again
♬直到我们再次相遇。
♪ Till we meet again.
魔鬼来找你了……
The devil is coming for you...
执法者。
lawman.
我并不难找，你个混蛋。
Well, I ain't hard to find, you sumbitch.
♬武装和危险
♪ Armed and dangerous
♬让我们骑，让我们骑，让我们骑，让我们骑
♪ Let's ride, let's ride, let's ride, let's ride ♪
♬武装和危险
♪ Armed and dangerous
♬让我们骑，让我们骑，让我们骑，让我们骑
♪ Let's ride, let's ride, let's ride, let's ride ♪
♪No-No-Notorious
♪ No-No-Notorious
♬让我们骑，让我们骑，让我们骑，让我们骑
♪ Let's ride, let's ride, let's ride, let's ride ♪
如果你不和我一起骑，你就不是我的兄弟
♪ If you ain't riding with me, you ain't my brother ♪
♬说他们和我在一起，但我知道他们并不忠诚
♪ Say they riding with me, but I know that they ain't loyal ♪
♬说他们是你的团队成员
♪ Say they on your team
但他们并不是真的支持你
♪ But they ain't really rooting for you ♪
♬当我骑马的时候把它带在我身上
♪ Keep it on me when I'm riding ♪
如果你和你一起滑，那么我也在滑
♪ If you gang and you sliding, then I'm sliding ♪
♬来吧，让我们去兜风，兜风，兜风，兜风
♪ Come on, let's take a ride, ride, ride, ride, ride ♪
♬我们一起骑吧，一起骑吧，一起骑吧
♪ Let's ride, let's ride, let's ride ♪
♬骑，骑，骑，骑，骑
♪ Ride, ride, ride, ride, ride
♬我们一起骑吧，一起骑吧，一起骑吧
♪ Let's ride, let's ride, let's ride ♪
♬唉，我开车的时候会踩油门
♪ Ay, I do the dash when I drive ♪
♬宝贝在上面，当她骑着车时，她做着冲刺
♪ Baby on top, she do the dash when she ride ♪
♬唉，我自尊心太高了
♪ Ay, my self-respect too high
如果你对我做错了，我们永远都不会对
♪ If you did me wrong, we could never get right ♪
♬没钱买爱，就得交税
♪ Can't pay for love, gotta pay my taxes ♪
♬我得付钱给我的暴徒，因为他们总是行动起来
♪ Gotta pay my thugs 'cause they 'bout action ♪
♬他应该是个电影明星，他擅长表演
♪ He should be a movie star, he good at actin' ♪
♬这是一个新时代，他们都在唱歌和说唱
♪ This a new era, they all cappin' and rappin' ♪
如果你不和我一起骑，你就不是我的兄弟
♪ If you ain't riding with me, you ain't my brother ♪
♬说他们和我在一起，但我知道他们并不忠诚
♪ Say they riding with me, but I know that they ain't loyal ♪
♬说他们是你的团队成员
♪ Say they on your team
但他们并不是真的支持你
♪ But they ain't really rooting for you ♪
♬当我骑马的时候把它带在我身上
♪ Keep it on me when I'm riding ♪
如果你和你一起滑，那么我也在滑
♪ If you gang and you sliding, then I'm sliding ♪
♬来吧，让我们去兜风，兜风，兜风，兜风
♪ Come on, let's take a ride, ride, ride, ride, ride ♪
♬我们一起骑吧，一起骑吧，一起骑吧
♪ Let's ride, let's ride, let's ride ♪
♬骑，骑，骑，骑，骑
♪ Ride, ride, ride, ride, ride
♬我们一起骑吧，一起骑吧，一起骑吧
♪ Let's ride, let's ride, let's ride ♪
告诉我它是做什么的，她会挑选的
♪ Tell me what it do, she gon' pick and choose ♪
♬原谅她站起来，开着吉普车
♪ Forgis on her feet, pulling up in Jeeps ♪
♬我骑得很深，我说:“宝贝，按下按钮。
♪ Riding four deep, I'm like, "Baby, push the button" ♪
♬一百在仪表盘上，我甚至都不用碰它
♪ Hundred on the dash, I ain't even had to touch it ♪
说到战争，告诉他们，“准备好”
♪ Talking 'bout war, told 'em, "Ready up" ♪
♬我骑得很快，我什么都不怕
♪ Whip I'm riding in fast, I ain't scared of nothin' ♪
告诉她，如果她想和我一起兜风，就来吧
♪ Told her if she wanna ride with me, come and get lost ♪
♬我知道她在跟老板闹着玩
♪ Know she messing with a boss
如果你不和我一起骑，你就不是我的兄弟
♪ If you ain't riding with me, you ain't my brother ♪
♬说他们和我在一起，但我知道他们并不忠诚
♪ Say they riding with me, but I know that they ain't loyal ♪
♬说他们是你的团队成员
♪ Say they on your team
但他们并不是真的支持你
♪ But they ain't really rooting for you ♪
♬当我骑马的时候把它带在我身上
♪ Keep it on me when I'm riding ♪
如果你和你一起滑，那么我也在滑
♪ If you gang and you sliding, then I'm sliding ♪
♬来吧，让我们去兜风，兜风，兜风，兜风
♪ Come on, let's take a ride, ride, ride, ride, ride ♪
♬我们一起骑吧，一起骑吧，一起骑吧
♪ Let's ride, let's ride, let's ride ♪
♬骑，骑，骑，骑，骑
♪ Ride, ride, ride, ride, ride
♬我们一起骑，一起骑，一起骑。♪
♪ Let's ride, let's ride, let's ride. ♪
♬哦，哦，哦，哦，哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
♬沉重的钻石眼
♪ Heavy diamond eyes
♬你能感觉到我的风暴吗?
♪ Can you feel my storm?
♬听到雷声响起
♪ Hear the thunder strike
♬看闪电滚
♪ See the lightning roll
♬和时间打赌输了
♪ Lost a bet with time
♬时钟快用完了
♪ Clock is running low
♬沉重的钻石眼
♪ Heavy diamond eyes
♬是时候让它们关闭了
♪ Time to let them close
♬哦，哦，哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh
♬哇，哦，哇，哦，哦，哦
♪ Whoa, oh, whoa, oh, oh, oh
♬最后什么都不重要了
♪ Nothing else matters in the end ♪
♬你没有生命线
♪ You don't have a lifeline
♬哦，这会把你逼到悬崖边的
♪ Oh, this is going to push you to the edge ♪
什么都不重要，别忘了
♪ Nothing else matters, don't forget ♪
♬你的时间是借来的
♪ You're running on borrowed time ♪
♬哦，看看你最后还剩下什么
♪ Oh, look at what you're left with in the end ♪
哦，这是一场输掉的比赛
♪ Oh, it's a losing game
♬但你现在已无法回头
♪ But you can't turn back now
♬你所有的救生艇都沉了
♪ All of your lifeboats sank
♬但你现在已无法回头
♪ But you can't turn back now
不能让它就这样结束
♪ Can't let it end this way
♬你现在不能回头了
♪ You can't turn back now
♬哦，哇，哇，哦，哦
♪ Oh, whoa, whoa, oh, oh
♬最后什么都不重要了
♪ Nothing else matters in the end ♪
♬你没有生命线
♪ You don't have a lifeline
♬哦，这会把你逼到悬崖边的
♪ Oh, this is going to push you to the edge ♪
什么都不重要，别忘了
♪ Nothing else matters, don't forget ♪
♬你的时间是借来的
♪ You're running on borrowed time ♪
♬哦，看看你最后还剩下什么
♪ Oh, look at what you're left with in the end ♪
♬哦，哦，哦，哦，哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
♬哦，哦，哦，哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh
♬哦，哦，哦。
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh.